[
  {
    "question": "Complete the sentence. A product that is … is popular at a particular time.",
    "options": [
      "mutual",
      "fashionable",
      "large",
      "basic",
      "poor"
    ],
    "answer": "fashionable"
  },
  {
    "question": "Complete the sentence. An … product is one that people find beautiful and exciting.",
    "options": [
      "economic",
      "attractive",
      "total",
      "low-quality",
      "poor"
    ],
    "answer": "attractive"
  },
  {
    "question": "Complete the sentence. An … product is expensive and usually of high quality.",
    "options": [
      "multipurpose",
      "upmarket",
      "quick",
      "downmarket",
      "accurate"
    ],
    "answer": "upmarket"
  },
  {
    "question": "Complete the sentence. These products are made to meat a need,…........",
    "options": [
      "contribute financially",
      "to satisfy consumer demand",
      "to answer the question",
      "respond differently",
      "economic output"
    ],
    "answer": "to satisfy consumer demand"
  },
  {
    "question": "Complete the sentence. Li Ning has strong sales and distribution…......in the lower-tier cities that Adidas hopes ….......",
    "options": [
      "targeting, to manufacture",
      "network, to penetrate",
      "retail, penetrate",
      "position, to rebrand",
      "growth, entry"
    ],
    "answer": "network, to penetrate"
  },
  {
    "question": "Choose the right preposition: I saw an ad …..a magazine and I liked the look ….it",
    "options": [
      "on, off",
      "in, of",
      "in, for",
      "at, in",
      "in, at"
    ],
    "answer": "in, of"
  },
  {
    "question": "Match the word or phrase to its definition: a promise or firm decision to do something",
    "options": [
      "punctuality",
      "commitment",
      "admit",
      "decide",
      "desire"
    ],
    "answer": "commitment"
  },
  {
    "question": "Choose the opposite for the word: domestic",
    "options": [
      "homelike",
      "foreign",
      "foreigner",
      "family",
      "interior"
    ],
    "answer": "foreign"
  },
  {
    "question": "Choose the right preposition. I think we should carry … a survey.",
    "options": [
      "but",
      "out",
      "at",
      "under",
      "if"
    ],
    "answer": "out"
  },
  {
    "question": "Complete the sentence: Smaller banks are struggling to compete in an already…market.",
    "options": [
      "retail",
      "saturated",
      "down",
      "product mix",
      "existing"
    ],
    "answer": "saturated"
  },
  {
    "question": "Match the two parts of the dialogue. When do you want to discuss the project?",
    "options": [
      "Yes, I have. I`d like to discuss it with you when you have a minute.",
      "Well, could we possibly do that before the meeting starts?",
      "No, never again. Certainly not until they apologise for their terrible mistakes.",
      "We don`t know yet. We`ll have more information after we`ve talked to the team leader.",
      "Yes, If anybody phones while I`m out, tell them I`ll be back by 1.30."
    ],
    "answer": "Well, could we possibly do that before the meeting starts?"
  },
  {
    "question": "Match the two parts of the dialogue. Have you read Peter`sales report?",
    "options": [
      "When you`ve typed them all up, we can check them together.",
      "Yes, I have. I`d like to discuss it with you when you have a minute.",
      "No, never again. Certainly not until they apologise for their terrible mistakes.",
      "We don`t know yet. We`ll have more information after we`ve talked to the team leader.",
      "Yes, I agree. We`ll find out as soon as we get the FT."
    ],
    "answer": "Yes, I have. I`d like to discuss it with you when you have a minute."
  },
  {
    "question": "Match the two parts of the dialogue. So have they won the contract, then?",
    "options": [
      "No, never again. Certainly not until they apologise for their terrible mistakes.",
      "We don`t know yet. We`ll have more information after we`ve talked to the team leader.",
      "When you`ve typed them all up, we can check them together.",
      "Well, could we possibly do that before the meeting starts?",
      "Yes, I agree. We`ll find out as soon as we get the FT."
    ],
    "answer": "We don`t know yet. We`ll have more information after we`ve talked to the team leader."
  },
  {
    "question": "Match the two parts of the dialogue. Are you going to the trade fair now?",
    "options": [
      "When you`ve typed them all up, we can check them together.",
      "Yes, If anybody phones while I`m out, tell them I`ll be back by 1.30.",
      "Yes, I agree. We`ll find out as soon as we get the FT.",
      "No, never again. Certainly not until they apologise for their terrible mistakes.",
      "Yes, I have. I`d like to discuss it with you when you have a minute."
    ],
    "answer": "Yes, If anybody phones while I`m out, tell them I`ll be back by 1.30."
  },
  {
    "question": "Choose the opposite for the word : upmarket",
    "options": [
      "trade market",
      "downmarket",
      "free market",
      "share market",
      "mass market"
    ],
    "answer": "downmarket"
  },
  {
    "question": "Match the word or word combination to its definition. A car company introduces a new model.",
    "options": [
      "breakdown",
      "product launch",
      "profit margin",
      "workload",
      "sales target"
    ],
    "answer": "product launch"
  },
  {
    "question": "Choose the right prepositions: I am also ……charge …… design budgets.",
    "options": [
      "in, with",
      "in, of",
      "of, with",
      "with, on",
      "for, of"
    ],
    "answer": "in, of"
  },
  {
    "question": "Complete the sentence: There are different ways you could improve your….......",
    "options": [
      "employment",
      "performance",
      "upmarket",
      "financial",
      "a customer"
    ],
    "answer": "performance"
  },
  {
    "question": "Match the word or word combination to its definition. The time when you can change your mind and cancel an order.",
    "options": [
      "method of payment",
      "cooling - off period",
      "money-back guarantee",
      "after-sales service",
      "credit-card details"
    ],
    "answer": "cooling - off period"
  },
  {
    "question": "Match the word or word combination to its definition. Method for customers to obtain a discount on future purchases from the same",
    "options": [
      "after-sales service",
      "loyalty-card scheme",
      "cooling - off period",
      "credit-card details",
      "method of payment"
    ],
    "answer": "loyalty-card scheme"
  },
  {
    "question": "Choose the right prepositions: Here are some expressions used …meetings …different purposes.",
    "options": [
      "at, in",
      "in, for",
      "on, to",
      "to, from",
      "for, to"
    ],
    "answer": "in, for"
  },
  {
    "question": "Choose the right prepositions. There are three candidates …the position …Sales and Marketing Director.",
    "options": [
      "for, at",
      "in, for",
      "at, for",
      "on, in",
      "for, of"
    ],
    "answer": "for, of"
  },
  {
    "question": "Complete the sentence: decides the amount of the bonus for each consultant.",
    "options": [
      "candidate",
      "the manager",
      "property",
      "client",
      "condition"
    ],
    "answer": "the manager"
  },
  {
    "question": "Choose the synonym of the word: proposal",
    "options": [
      "admit",
      "suggestion",
      "bribe",
      "aim",
      "target"
    ],
    "answer": "suggestion"
  },
  {
    "question": "Choose the right conjunction. The motivation of the sales is now increasing …...we bought some new company cars.",
    "options": [
      "so",
      "because",
      "because of",
      "but",
      "though"
    ],
    "answer": "because"
  },
  {
    "question": "Choose the right conjunction. There is a steady growth in sales ….. profits are not rising.",
    "options": [
      "though",
      "but",
      "so",
      "because of",
      "because"
    ],
    "answer": "but"
  },
  {
    "question": "Choose the right conjunction. Sales were not as good as they had hoped ..... they launched a marketing campaign.",
    "options": [
      "as",
      "so",
      "yet",
      "for",
      "because"
    ],
    "answer": "so"
  },
  {
    "question": "Choose the right prepositions: ….regard ….price, we should look carefully ….our competitors` policy.",
    "options": [
      "to, for, in",
      "with, to, at",
      "in, at, for",
      "at, in, of",
      "on, of, with"
    ],
    "answer": "with, to, at"
  },
  {
    "question": "Complete the sentence. Don`t make .... claims - don`t say things are better than they really are.",
    "options": [
      "confident",
      "exaggerated",
      "structured",
      "better",
      "negative"
    ],
    "answer": "exaggerated"
  },
  {
    "question": "Match the phrase to its definition. The amount of money that company makes in a period of time.",
    "options": [
      "provision",
      "turnover",
      "refund",
      "receipt",
      "estimate"
    ],
    "answer": "turnover"
  },
  {
    "question": "Complete the sentence: They receive immediate ..... from a finance house.",
    "options": [
      "policy",
      "payment",
      "budget",
      "deposit",
      "impact"
    ],
    "answer": "payment"
  },
  {
    "question": "Match the phrase to its definition. A shop that sells a range of everyday items and is open long hours.",
    "options": [
      "an online retailer",
      "a convenience store",
      "banks",
      "a specialist retailer",
      "a department store"
    ],
    "answer": "a convenience store"
  },
  {
    "question": "Match the word to its definition. A person or company that sells goods in large quantities to businesses.",
    "options": [
      "individuals",
      "wholesaler",
      "consumer",
      "traders",
      "sales assistant"
    ],
    "answer": "wholesaler"
  },
  {
    "question": "Match the word to its definition. To discuss and agree the price of something.",
    "options": [
      "to start",
      "to bargain",
      "to stop",
      "to work",
      "to bring forward a meeting"
    ],
    "answer": "to bargain"
  },
  {
    "question": "Complete the sentence. Increased production and strong demand have had a positive effect on our ….....",
    "options": [
      "cash flow",
      "contact",
      "refund",
      "problem",
      "hierarchy"
    ],
    "answer": "cash flow"
  },
  {
    "question": "Match the word or phrase to its definition. An agreement reached through negotiation.",
    "options": [
      "foreign investment",
      "bargain",
      "consumer spending",
      "political situation",
      "formality"
    ],
    "answer": "bargain"
  },
  {
    "question": "Complete the sentence with the correct ending. They don`t have an online catalogue…..",
    "options": [
      "which means they don`t have to queue.",
      "so we have to ask them to send us one.",
      "so she won`t have to drive to work anymore.",
      "so we had to order some more.",
      "so we didn`t have to discuss the deal any further."
    ],
    "answer": "so we have to ask them to send us one."
  },
  {
    "question": "Match the word partnership to its definition. The percentage of sales a company has.",
    "options": [
      "market segment",
      "market share",
      "market research",
      "market price",
      "market basket"
    ],
    "answer": "market share"
  },
  {
    "question": "Match the word partnership to its definition. Information about what customers want and need.",
    "options": [
      "market price",
      "market research",
      "market share",
      "market basket",
      "market segment"
    ],
    "answer": "market research"
  },
  {
    "question": "Match the word partnership to its definition. A group of customers of similar age, income level and social group.",
    "options": [
      "market basket",
      "market segment",
      "market price",
      "market share",
      "market research"
    ],
    "answer": "market segment"
  },
  {
    "question": "Match the word partnership to its definition. Description of a typical customer.",
    "options": [
      "consumer price",
      "consumer profile",
      "consumer goods",
      "consumer tax",
      "consumer behaviour"
    ],
    "answer": "consumer profile"
  },
  {
    "question": "Match the word partnership to its definition. Where and how people buy things.",
    "options": [
      "consumer goods",
      "consumer behaviour",
      "consumer profile",
      "consumer tax",
      "consumer price"
    ],
    "answer": "consumer behaviour"
  },
  {
    "question": "Match the word partnership to its definition. Things people buy for their own use.",
    "options": [
      "consumer tax",
      "consumer goods",
      "consumer price",
      "consumer behaviour",
      "consumer profile"
    ],
    "answer": "consumer goods"
  },
  {
    "question": "Match the word partnership to its definition. Introduction of a product to the market.",
    "options": [
      "product price",
      "product launch",
      "product range",
      "product manager",
      "product lifecycle"
    ],
    "answer": "product launch"
  },
  {
    "question": "Match the word partnership to its definition. Length of time people continue to buy a product.",
    "options": [
      "product manager",
      "product lifecycle",
      "product price",
      "product range",
      "product launch"
    ],
    "answer": "product lifecycle"
  },
  {
    "question": "Match the word partnership to its definition. Set of products made by a company.",
    "options": [
      "product launch",
      "product price",
      "product lifecycle",
      "product range",
      "product manager"
    ],
    "answer": "product range"
  },
  {
    "question": "Match the word partnership to its definition. How much a company wants to sell in a period.",
    "options": [
      "sales manager",
      "sales target",
      "sales figures",
      "sales tax",
      "sales forecast"
    ],
    "answer": "sales target"
  },
  {
    "question": "Match the word partnership to its definition. How much a company thinks it will sell in a period.",
    "options": [
      "sales tax",
      "sales figures",
      "sales target",
      "sales forecast",
      "sales manager"
    ],
    "answer": "sales forecast"
  },
  {
    "question": "Match the word partnership to its definition. Numbers showing how much a company has sold in a period.",
    "options": [
      "sales target",
      "sales figures",
      "sales manager",
      "sales forecast",
      "sales tax"
    ],
    "answer": "sales figures"
  },
  {
    "question": "Match the word partnership to its definition. A business which advises companies on advertising and makes ads.",
    "options": [
      "advertising standards",
      "advertising agency",
      "advertising campaign",
      "advertising agent",
      "advertising budget"
    ],
    "answer": "advertising agency"
  },
  {
    "question": "Complete the sentence: The Wincote XWS ..... at the right segment of the market.",
    "options": [
      "is in charge",
      "is targeted",
      "changes",
      "will be direct",
      "has designed"
    ],
    "answer": "is targeted"
  },
  {
    "question": "Complete the sentence. Was this product ..... the correct way?",
    "options": [
      "price fixing",
      "promoted",
      "guide",
      "buying",
      "approached"
    ],
    "answer": "promoted"
  },
  {
    "question": "Complete the sentence: The Wincote XWS is targeted at the right… of the market.",
    "options": [
      "market share",
      "segment",
      "goods",
      "figures",
      "changes"
    ],
    "answer": "segment"
  },
  {
    "question": "Choose the synonym of the word: to be aimed",
    "options": [
      "to be continued",
      "to be targeted",
      "to approach",
      "received",
      "acceptance"
    ],
    "answer": "to be targeted"
  },
  {
    "question": "Choose the right conjunction. Local competition is extremely strong …..we are planning to buy out local competitors.",
    "options": [
      "because of",
      "so",
      "though",
      "because",
      "as"
    ],
    "answer": "so"
  },
  {
    "question": "Choose the right conjunction. It is a difficult time for the industry …… our company is still growing.",
    "options": [
      "because",
      "but",
      "as",
      "for",
      "because of"
    ],
    "answer": "but"
  },
  {
    "question": "Match the word partnership to its definition. An amount of money available for advertising during a particular period.",
    "options": [
      "advertising agency",
      "advertising budget",
      "advertising standards",
      "advertising campaign",
      "advertising agent"
    ],
    "answer": "advertising budget"
  },
  {
    "question": "Complete the sentence with the correct ending. They usually order online….",
    "options": [
      "so we didn`t have to discuss the deal any further.",
      "which means they don`t have to queue.",
      "so she won`t have to drive to work anymore.",
      "so we have to ask them to send us one.",
      "so we had to order some more."
    ],
    "answer": "which means they don`t have to queue."
  },
  {
    "question": "Complete the sentence with the correct ending. We didn`t have any more paper in stock ……",
    "options": [
      "so she won`t have to drive to work anymore.",
      "so we had to order some more.",
      "which means they don`t have to queue.",
      "so we didn`t have to discuss the deal any further.",
      "so we`ll have to exchange them."
    ],
    "answer": "so we had to order some more."
  },
  {
    "question": "Complete the sentence with the correct ending. Her new flat is near her workplace…….",
    "options": [
      "so we had to order some more.",
      "so she won`t have to drive to work anymore.",
      "which means they don`t have to queue.",
      "so we have to ask them to send us one.",
      "so we didn`t have to discuss the deal any further."
    ],
    "answer": "so she won`t have to drive to work anymore."
  },
  {
    "question": "Complete the sentence with the correct ending. They say some of the goods are damaged…..",
    "options": [
      "so we had to order some more.",
      "so we didn`t have to discuss the deal any further.",
      "so we`ll have to exchange them.",
      "which means they don`t have to queue.",
      "so she won`t have to drive to work anymore."
    ],
    "answer": "so we`ll have to exchange them."
  },
  {
    "question": "Complete the sentence with the correct ending. We were all in agreement ….",
    "options": [
      "which means they don`t have to queue.",
      "so we didn`t have to discuss the deal any further.",
      "so we had to order some more.",
      "so we have to ask them to send us one.",
      "so she won`t have to drive to work anymore."
    ],
    "answer": "so we didn`t have to discuss the deal any further."
  },
  {
    "question": "Match the word or word combination to its definition. An area or building with a number of shops.",
    "options": [
      "organizations",
      "shopping center",
      "stock market",
      "financial market",
      "stock house"
    ],
    "answer": "shopping center"
  },
  {
    "question": "Match the word or word combination to its definition. Another name for a /producer/",
    "options": [
      "caller",
      "manufacturer",
      "buyer",
      "seller",
      "cook"
    ],
    "answer": "manufacturer"
  },
  {
    "question": "Match the word or word combination to its definition. A promise to return your money if you are not happy.",
    "options": [
      "method of payment",
      "money-back guarantee",
      "after-sales service",
      "credit-card details",
      "cooling - off period"
    ],
    "answer": "money-back guarantee"
  },
  {
    "question": "Match the word or word combination to its definition. The way you pay for the goods you want.",
    "options": [
      "cooling - off period",
      "method of payment",
      "credit-card details",
      "after-sales service",
      "loyalty-card scheme"
    ],
    "answer": "method of payment"
  },
  {
    "question": "Match the word or word combination to its definition. The help you get from a company when you start to use their product.",
    "options": [
      "cooling - off period",
      "after-sales service",
      "method of payment",
      "loyalty-card scheme",
      "credit-card details"
    ],
    "answer": "after-sales service"
  },
  {
    "question": "Match the word or word combination to its definition. The name, number and expiry date on your payment card.",
    "options": [
      "cooling - off period",
      "credit-card details",
      "method of payment",
      "loyalty-card scheme",
      "after-sales service"
    ],
    "answer": "credit-card details"
  },
  {
    "question": "Complete the sentence: Always ..... the small print before you sign a sales contract.",
    "options": [
      "damage",
      "read",
      "have",
      "write",
      "order"
    ],
    "answer": "read"
  },
  {
    "question": "Complete the sentence: … is a request by a customer for goods or services.",
    "options": [
      "workplace",
      "order",
      "regard",
      "activity",
      "hospitality"
    ],
    "answer": "order"
  },
  {
    "question": "Complete the sentence. He has a strong desire to succeed. He is totally……….",
    "options": [
      "serious",
      "ambitious",
      "impatient",
      "flexible",
      "interested"
    ],
    "answer": "ambitious"
  },
  {
    "question": "Make up the sentence: companies/ Many/ completely/ month/ down/ that/ close.",
    "options": [
      "Many that month companies down completely close.",
      "Many companies close down completely that month.",
      "Down many companies that completely close month.",
      "Many completely month companies that down close.",
      "Companies close many completely down that month."
    ],
    "answer": "Many companies close down completely that month."
  },
  {
    "question": "Match the word partnership to its definition. A programme of advertising activities over a period, with particular aims.",
    "options": [
      "advertising standards",
      "advertising campaign",
      "advertising agency",
      "advertising agent",
      "advertising budget"
    ],
    "answer": "advertising campaign"
  },
  {
    "question": "Match the word to its definition. The cost to the buyer of goods or services.",
    "options": [
      "service",
      "price",
      "product",
      "place",
      "promotion"
    ],
    "answer": "price"
  },
  {
    "question": "Match the word to its definition. Informing customers about products and persuading them to buy them.",
    "options": [
      "price",
      "promotion",
      "place",
      "service",
      "product"
    ],
    "answer": "promotion"
  },
  {
    "question": "Match the word to its definition. Where goods or services are available.",
    "options": [
      "product",
      "place",
      "promotion",
      "price",
      "service"
    ],
    "answer": "place"
  },
  {
    "question": "Match the word to its definition. Goods or services that are sold.",
    "options": [
      "promotion",
      "product",
      "service",
      "place",
      "price"
    ],
    "answer": "product"
  },
  {
    "question": "Complete the sentence. Companies sometimes promote their products by giving ……. gifts to customers.",
    "options": [
      "need",
      "free",
      "promotion",
      "aim",
      "forecast"
    ],
    "answer": "free"
  },
  {
    "question": "Complete the sentence. Companies carry out market research to get information about what buyers …… and want.",
    "options": [
      "share",
      "need",
      "sales",
      "place",
      "promotion"
    ],
    "answer": "need"
  },
  {
    "question": "Complete the sentence. Good marketing should increase the volume of ……… .",
    "options": [
      "forecast",
      "sales",
      "need",
      "promotion",
      "place"
    ],
    "answer": "sales"
  },
  {
    "question": "Complete the sentence. Production …… are what a company must spend on production.",
    "options": [
      "cycle",
      "costs",
      "forecast",
      "place",
      "need"
    ],
    "answer": "costs"
  },
  {
    "question": "Complete the sentence. An advertising campaign takes place over a period of time and usually has specific …. .",
    "options": [
      "share",
      "aim",
      "lifestyle",
      "place",
      "packaging"
    ],
    "answer": "aim"
  },
  {
    "question": "Match the word or phrase to its definition. The combination of products that a company has to offer.",
    "options": [
      "disposable income",
      "product mix",
      "saturated",
      "upmarket",
      "rebrand"
    ],
    "answer": "product mix"
  },
  {
    "question": "Match the word or phrase to its definition. A market filled so completely that no more products can be added.",
    "options": [
      "market position",
      "product mix",
      "disposable income",
      "saturated",
      "penetrate"
    ],
    "answer": "saturated"
  },
  {
    "question": "Match the word or phrase to its definition. Expensive compared to other products of the same type.",
    "options": [
      "disposable income",
      "upmarket",
      "rebrand",
      "market position",
      "penetrate"
    ],
    "answer": "upmarket"
  },
  {
    "question": "Match the word or phrase to its definition. Start selling goods or services in a new market.",
    "options": [
      "product mix",
      "penetrate",
      "saturated",
      "disposable income",
      "upmarket"
    ],
    "answer": "penetrate"
  },
  {
    "question": "Match the word or phrase to its definition. Money that is available to spend after paying for essentials like taxes, food and housing.",
    "options": [
      "upmarket",
      "disposable income",
      "penetrate",
      "market position",
      "rebrand"
    ],
    "answer": "disposable income"
  },
  {
    "question": "Match the word or phrase to its definition. The ranking of a company or brand against its competitors in terms of its sales.",
    "options": [
      "rebrand",
      "market position",
      "product mix",
      "saturated",
      "upmarket"
    ],
    "answer": "market position"
  },
  {
    "question": "Complete the sentence. In our very ….business world, a good brand is one of the keys to the success of any company.",
    "options": [
      "possible",
      "competitive",
      "saturated",
      "informative",
      "domestic"
    ],
    "answer": "competitive"
  },
  {
    "question": "Complete the sentence. ……did you launch this advertising campaign?",
    "options": [
      "how many",
      "when",
      "which",
      "what",
      "how much"
    ],
    "answer": "when"
  },
  {
    "question": "Complete the sentence. ……didn`t you contact an advertising agency?",
    "options": [
      "what",
      "why",
      "how much",
      "which",
      "who"
    ],
    "answer": "why"
  },
  {
    "question": "Complete the sentence. ……money did you spend on the campaign?",
    "options": [
      "how many",
      "how much",
      "when",
      "how long",
      "why"
    ],
    "answer": "how much"
  },
  {
    "question": "Complete the sentence. ……new products did you launch? Was it two or three?",
    "options": [
      "how long",
      "how many",
      "how much",
      "why",
      "who"
    ],
    "answer": "how many"
  },
  {
    "question": "Complete the sentence. ……did you target your new product at?",
    "options": [
      "how many",
      "who",
      "how",
      "what",
      "how much"
    ],
    "answer": "who"
  },
  {
    "question": "Choose the right preposition: If a product is …...sale .... a John Lewis store, you know you can trust it.",
    "options": [
      "for, on",
      "on, in",
      "at, at",
      "on, with",
      "on, of"
    ],
    "answer": "on, in"
  },
  {
    "question": "Choose the right preposition: We are one .... the largest mobile-phone retailers in Europe.",
    "options": [
      "at",
      "of",
      "for",
      "with",
      "from"
    ],
    "answer": "of"
  },
  {
    "question": "Use the explanation to choose the correct verb. The government is encouraging people to …..new business. (start)",
    "options": [
      "put off",
      "looked for",
      "set up",
      "gave up",
      "came up with"
    ],
    "answer": "set up"
  },
  {
    "question": "Choose the synonym of the word: run",
    "options": [
      "cancel",
      "chair",
      "increase",
      "share",
      "confuse"
    ],
    "answer": "chair"
  },
  {
    "question": "Make up the sentence: wants/ productive/ be/ achieve/ everyone/ results/ meetings/ to/ and",
    "options": [
      "Meetings wants to achieve productive results and be everyone.",
      "Everyone wants meetings to be productive and achieve results.",
      "To wants productive and everyone meetings achieve be results.",
      "Be productive results and wants everyone to achieve meetings.",
      "Productive wants and be everyone results to achieve meetings."
    ],
    "answer": "Everyone wants meetings to be productive and achieve results."
  },
  {
    "question": "Complete the sentence: If there is demand for shares in a company, its share price ….",
    "options": [
      "rise",
      "goes up",
      "decreases",
      "falls",
      "goes down"
    ],
    "answer": "goes up"
  },
  {
    "question": "Match the word to its definition. Buying and selling of shares.",
    "options": [
      "selling",
      "trading",
      "distribution",
      "decline",
      "overstocking"
    ],
    "answer": "trading"
  },
  {
    "question": "Complete the sentence: Ambitious people often .... on a career plan while they are still at university.",
    "options": [
      "have",
      "decide",
      "take",
      "make",
      "offer"
    ],
    "answer": "decide"
  },
  {
    "question": "Complete the sentence: Espania-pharm today announced the opening of its new… in Barcelona.",
    "options": [
      "turnover",
      "head office",
      "global giant",
      "working environment",
      "workload"
    ],
    "answer": "head office"
  },
  {
    "question": "Choose the right preposition. Thank you all once again ….. your continuing support of the company.",
    "options": [
      "by",
      "for",
      "in",
      "at",
      "to"
    ],
    "answer": "for"
  },
  {
    "question": "Match the word to its definition. The ability to change according to the situation.",
    "options": [
      "outspoken",
      "flexibility",
      "kind",
      "decisive",
      "numerate"
    ],
    "answer": "flexibility"
  },
  {
    "question": "Choose the synonym of the word: head office",
    "options": [
      "subsidiary",
      "main building",
      "workplace",
      "company",
      "recession"
    ],
    "answer": "main building"
  },
  {
    "question": "Choose the right prepositions. We have moved …our new head office …central London.",
    "options": [
      "on, in",
      "to, in",
      "at, in",
      "in, to",
      "to, at"
    ],
    "answer": "to, in"
  },
  {
    "question": "Choose the right prepositions. I've learned a lot … lessons ... the companies I've worked ....",
    "options": [
      "of, of, from",
      "of, from, for",
      "of, at, from",
      "in, for, in",
      "from, of, to"
    ],
    "answer": "of, from, for"
  },
  {
    "question": "Match the companies to the industry sector they belong to. Lenovo, Apple, Dell, Microsoft.",
    "options": [
      "Pharmaceuticals",
      "IT ( Information Technology)",
      "Engineering",
      "Retail",
      "Electronics"
    ],
    "answer": "IT ( Information Technology)"
  },
  {
    "question": "Match the companies to the industry sector they belong to. Bayer, Johnson & Johnson, Novartis",
    "options": [
      "Retail",
      "Pharmaceuticals",
      "Electronics",
      "Transport",
      "IT ( Information Technology)"
    ],
    "answer": "Pharmaceuticals"
  },
  {
    "question": "Match the companies to the industry sector they belong to. BMW, General Motors, Nissan, Toyota.",
    "options": [
      "Retail",
      "Engineering",
      "IT ( Information Technology)",
      "Pharmaceuticals",
      "Banking and finance"
    ],
    "answer": "Engineering"
  },
  {
    "question": "Match the companies to the industry sector they belong to. Qatar Airways, Ryanair.",
    "options": [
      "Electronics",
      "Transport",
      "IT ( Information Technology)",
      "Banking and finance",
      "Pharmaceuticals"
    ],
    "answer": "Transport"
  },
  {
    "question": "Match the companies to the industry sector they belong to. HSBC, ING.",
    "options": [
      "Engineering",
      "Banking and finance",
      "Transport",
      "IT ( Information Technology)",
      "Retail"
    ],
    "answer": "Banking and finance"
  },
  {
    "question": "Match the companies to the industry sector they belong to. LG, Nokia, Samsung, Siemens.",
    "options": [
      "Pharmaceuticals",
      "Electronics",
      "Retail",
      "Banking and finance",
      "Transport"
    ],
    "answer": "Electronics"
  },
  {
    "question": "Match the word combination to its definition. The percentage of sales a company has in a particular market.",
    "options": [
      "turnover",
      "market share",
      "subsidiary",
      "net profit",
      "share price"
    ],
    "answer": "market share"
  },
  {
    "question": "Complete the sentence. ……market segments has your product been most successful in?",
    "options": [
      "why",
      "which",
      "who",
      "how much",
      "whose"
    ],
    "answer": "which"
  },
  {
    "question": "Complete the sentence. ……do you expect people to continue to buy this product?",
    "options": [
      "when",
      "how long",
      "how many",
      "who",
      "what"
    ],
    "answer": "how long"
  },
  {
    "question": "Complete the sentence. ……is your sales forecast?",
    "options": [
      "which",
      "what",
      "who",
      "why",
      "how"
    ],
    "answer": "what"
  },
  {
    "question": "Make up the sentence: a/ advertising/ Do/ lot/ on/ spend/ they?",
    "options": [
      "Do spend a lot they advertising on?",
      "Do they spend a lot on advertising?",
      "Do they a spend advertising on lot?",
      "Do a lot advertising on they spend?",
      "Do a lot on they spend advertising?"
    ],
    "answer": "Do they spend a lot on advertising?"
  },
  {
    "question": "Make up the sentence: expecting/ figures/ sales/ Were/ better/ you?",
    "options": [
      "Were sales you expecting better figures?",
      "Were you expecting better sales figures?",
      "Were expecting better you figures sales?",
      "Were better you sales figures expecting?",
      "Were figures you expecting better sales?"
    ],
    "answer": "Were you expecting better sales figures?"
  },
  {
    "question": "Make up the sentence: my/ Have/ sales/ read/ report/ you/ quarterly?",
    "options": [
      "Have sales my report quarterly you read?",
      "Have you read my quarterly sales report?",
      "Have you quarterly sales read my report?",
      "Have my read you quarterly report sales?",
      "Have read you my sales quarterly sales report?"
    ],
    "answer": "Have you read my quarterly sales report?"
  },
  {
    "question": "Make up the sentence: a/ How/ do/ often/ report/ write/ you?",
    "options": [
      "How do often you write a report?",
      "How often you report do write a?",
      "How a report do you write often?",
      "How write a report do you often?",
      "How often do you write a report?"
    ],
    "answer": "How often do you write a report?"
  },
  {
    "question": "Choose the right prepositions: The key ….successful marketing consists….three broad areas.",
    "options": [
      "of, with",
      "to, of",
      "on, for",
      "in, on",
      "at, in"
    ],
    "answer": "to, of"
  },
  {
    "question": "Choose the right prepositions: I am interested ….your range …diet products.",
    "options": [
      "at, to",
      "in, of",
      "on, for",
      "for, on",
      "of, in"
    ],
    "answer": "in, of"
  },
  {
    "question": "Choose the right prepositions: Present your ideas ... the other teams …. the marketing department.",
    "options": [
      "at, to",
      "to, in",
      "for, of",
      "of, on",
      "with, in"
    ],
    "answer": "to, in"
  },
  {
    "question": "Complete the sentence. Could you …….us have your previous employer's details?",
    "options": [
      "working",
      "let",
      "send",
      "contact",
      "moving"
    ],
    "answer": "let"
  },
  {
    "question": "Choose the synonym of the word: purchase",
    "options": [
      "pressure",
      "buy",
      "compete",
      "receive",
      "send"
    ],
    "answer": "buy"
  },
  {
    "question": "Choose the synonym of the word: product range",
    "options": [
      "productivity",
      "assortment of products",
      "product launch",
      "share price",
      "hierarchy"
    ],
    "answer": "assortment of products"
  },
  {
    "question": "Choose the right prepositions: Did she talk ….you ….her plans to leave the company?",
    "options": [
      "for, on",
      "to, about",
      "with, on",
      "in, from",
      "by, at"
    ],
    "answer": "to, about"
  },
  {
    "question": "Match the sentence halves. We need to stay - ……",
    "options": [
      "and leave",
      "until the meeting has finished.",
      "when she will be promoted.",
      "try to stay calm.",
      "the economy will slow down."
    ],
    "answer": "until the meeting has finished."
  },
  {
    "question": "Complete the sentence. A fashion designer ….created the \"little black dress\" was a genius.",
    "options": [
      "where",
      "who",
      "when",
      "why",
      "what"
    ],
    "answer": "who"
  },
  {
    "question": "Complete the sentence. A brand is a name ….makes it easy for customers to recognise a product.",
    "options": [
      "who",
      "which",
      "why",
      "where",
      "when"
    ],
    "answer": "which"
  },
  {
    "question": "Complete the sentence. A warehouse is a large building ….goods are stored until they are distributed to shops to be sold.",
    "options": [
      "which",
      "where",
      "when",
      "why",
      "who"
    ],
    "answer": "where"
  },
  {
    "question": "Complete the sentence. A recession is a period of time ….the economy is doing badly.",
    "options": [
      "what",
      "why",
      "who",
      "when",
      "where"
    ],
    "answer": "when"
  },
  {
    "question": "Complete the sentence. This new instant coffee has been produced by a well-known company ….has always sold its coffee in the higher",
    "options": [
      "which",
      "when",
      "where",
      "who",
      "why"
    ],
    "answer": "which"
  },
  {
    "question": "Match the companies to the industry sector they belong to. Ikea, Tesco, Wal-Mart, Zara.",
    "options": [
      "Engineering",
      "Retail",
      "IT ( Information Technology)",
      "Banking and finance",
      "Transport"
    ],
    "answer": "Retail"
  },
  {
    "question": "Match the word or word combination to its definition. The main building or location of a large organization.",
    "options": [
      "subsidiary",
      "head office",
      "parent company",
      "turnover",
      "workforce"
    ],
    "answer": "head office"
  },
  {
    "question": "Match the word or word combination to its definition. The cost of a company’s shares.",
    "options": [
      "market share",
      "share price",
      "turnover",
      "subsidiary",
      "workforce"
    ],
    "answer": "share price"
  },
  {
    "question": "Match the word or word combination to its definition. The employees in a particular country or business.",
    "options": [
      "subsidiary",
      "workforce",
      "head office",
      "turnover",
      "market share"
    ],
    "answer": "workforce"
  },
  {
    "question": "Match the word or word combination to its definition. A company which owns another company.",
    "options": [
      "subsidiary",
      "parent company",
      "head office",
      "market share",
      "turnover"
    ],
    "answer": "parent company"
  },
  {
    "question": "Match the word or word combination to its definition. The amount of money a company receives from sales in a particular period.",
    "options": [
      "subsidiary",
      "turnover",
      "workforce",
      "net profit",
      "share price"
    ],
    "answer": "turnover"
  },
  {
    "question": "Match the word or word combination to its definition. The money the company makes after taking away its costs and tax.",
    "options": [
      "share price",
      "net profit",
      "turnover",
      "market share",
      "subsidiary"
    ],
    "answer": "net profit"
  },
  {
    "question": "Match the word combination to its definition. A company which is more than 50% owned by another company",
    "options": [
      "turnover",
      "subsidiary",
      "market segment",
      "workforce",
      "market share"
    ],
    "answer": "subsidiary"
  },
  {
    "question": "Match the sentence with the right meaning. Ms Delgado is replacing Sandra as Office Manager until next Friday.",
    "options": [
      "future arrangement",
      "temporary situation",
      "ongoing situation",
      "routine activity",
      "factual information"
    ],
    "answer": "temporary situation"
  },
  {
    "question": "Match the sentence with the right meaning. We are opening our sixth subsidiary next month.",
    "options": [
      "temporary situation",
      "future arrangement",
      "factual information",
      "ongoing situation",
      "routine activity"
    ],
    "answer": "future arrangement"
  },
  {
    "question": "Choose the right prepositions: Anne-Marie Duval works …a firm …management consultants.",
    "options": [
      "with, for",
      "for, of",
      "by, at",
      "on, for",
      "with, in"
    ],
    "answer": "for, of"
  },
  {
    "question": "Complete the sentence. The other reason for our success is the way we ..... our business.",
    "options": [
      "running",
      "run",
      "climb",
      "demand",
      "pressure"
    ],
    "answer": "run"
  },
  {
    "question": "Complete the sentence. She always has ideas and easily finds solutions to problems. She is a very .... person.",
    "options": [
      "calm",
      "flexible",
      "impatient",
      "creative",
      "ambitious"
    ],
    "answer": "creative"
  },
  {
    "question": "Complete the sentence. He is good with numbers. He is…..",
    "options": [
      "weak",
      "numerate",
      "flexible",
      "creative",
      "enthusiastic"
    ],
    "answer": "numerate"
  },
  {
    "question": "Complete the sentence. He is very good at… team spirit and cooperation.",
    "options": [
      "thinking",
      "encouraging",
      "treating",
      "delivering",
      "help"
    ],
    "answer": "encouraging"
  },
  {
    "question": "Complete the sentence: I can’t find a solution to all problems, of course, but I … my best.",
    "options": [
      "make",
      "do",
      "decide",
      "increase",
      "sell"
    ],
    "answer": "do"
  },
  {
    "question": "Complete the sentence: A lot of people want to … part time work when they retire.",
    "options": [
      "launch",
      "do",
      "deliver",
      "treat",
      "break"
    ],
    "answer": "do"
  },
  {
    "question": "Complete the sentence: The position will involve…..travel in the three countries.",
    "options": [
      "not",
      "frequent",
      "frequency",
      "language",
      "frequently"
    ],
    "answer": "frequent"
  },
  {
    "question": "Choose the right prepositions: We can return …this issue …the next meeting.",
    "options": [
      "on, to",
      "to, at",
      "on, in",
      "in, on",
      "at, in"
    ],
    "answer": "to, at"
  },
  {
    "question": "Choose the synonym of the word: dynamic",
    "options": [
      "lazy",
      "energetic",
      "decisive",
      "talkative",
      "energy"
    ],
    "answer": "energetic"
  },
  {
    "question": "Match the word combination to its definition. Chances to start improve your career.",
    "options": [
      "career move",
      "career opportunities",
      "career path",
      "career break",
      "career plan"
    ],
    "answer": "career opportunities"
  },
  {
    "question": "Match the word combination to its definition. Ideas you have for your career.",
    "options": [
      "career break",
      "career plan",
      "career move",
      "career path",
      "career opportunities"
    ],
    "answer": "career plan"
  },
  {
    "question": "Complete the sentence. The shop floor is an area in a factory ….ordinary workers do their work.",
    "options": [
      "when",
      "where",
      "who",
      "why",
      "what"
    ],
    "answer": "where"
  },
  {
    "question": "Complete the sentence. A retailer is a person ….owns or runs a shop selling goods to members of the public.",
    "options": [
      "where",
      "who",
      "what",
      "when",
      "why"
    ],
    "answer": "who"
  },
  {
    "question": "Complete the sentence. Sick leave is a period of time ….you stay away from your job because you are ill.",
    "options": [
      "where",
      "when",
      "why",
      "who",
      "which"
    ],
    "answer": "when"
  },
  {
    "question": "Choose the right preposition. Prices ….. Zimbabwe have risen sharply.",
    "options": [
      "upon",
      "on",
      "in",
      "to",
      "with"
    ],
    "answer": "in"
  },
  {
    "question": "Choose the right preposition: The Central Bank has reduced interest rates…0.5 per cent.",
    "options": [
      "in",
      "by",
      "with",
      "up",
      "on"
    ],
    "answer": "by"
  },
  {
    "question": "Match the economic term to its definition. Total value of goods and services produced in a country.",
    "options": [
      "tax incentives",
      "GDP(gross domestic product)",
      "unemployment rate",
      "balance of trade",
      "inflation rate"
    ],
    "answer": "GDP(gross domestic product)"
  },
  {
    "question": "Match the economic term to its definition. Percentage increase in prices.",
    "options": [
      "government bureaucracy",
      "inflation rate",
      "interest rate",
      "unemployment rate",
      "tax incentives"
    ],
    "answer": "inflation rate"
  },
  {
    "question": "Match the economic term to its definition. Cost of borrowing money.",
    "options": [
      "GDP(gross domestic product)",
      "interest rate",
      "balance of trade",
      "labour force",
      "exchange rate"
    ],
    "answer": "interest rate"
  },
  {
    "question": "Match the economic term to its definition. Price at which one currency can buy another.",
    "options": [
      "GDP(gross domestic product)",
      "exchange rate",
      "unemployment rate",
      "tax incentives",
      "inflation rate"
    ],
    "answer": "exchange rate"
  },
  {
    "question": "Match the economic term to its definition. Percentage of people without jobs.",
    "options": [
      "labour force",
      "unemployment rate",
      "tax incentives",
      "inflation rate",
      "foreign investment"
    ],
    "answer": "unemployment rate"
  },
  {
    "question": "Match the economic term to its definition. The number of people working.",
    "options": [
      "exchange rate",
      "labour force",
      "balance of trade",
      "unemployment rate",
      "government bureaucracy"
    ],
    "answer": "labour force"
  },
  {
    "question": "Match the economic term to its definition. Low taxes to encourage business activity.",
    "options": [
      "exchange rate",
      "tax incentives",
      "foreign investment",
      "government bureaucracy",
      "interest rate"
    ],
    "answer": "tax incentives"
  },
  {
    "question": "Match the economic term to its definition. Money from overseas.",
    "options": [
      "unemployment rate",
      "foreign investment",
      "balance of trade",
      "interest rate",
      "inflation rate"
    ],
    "answer": "foreign investment"
  },
  {
    "question": "Match the economic term to its definition. Official rules/ regulations/ paperwork.",
    "options": [
      "foreign investment",
      "government bureaucracy",
      "GDP(gross domestic product)",
      "exchange rate",
      "labour force"
    ],
    "answer": "government bureaucracy"
  },
  {
    "question": "Match the economic term to its definition. Difference in value between a country's imports and exports.",
    "options": [
      "unemployment rate",
      "balance of trade",
      "inflation rate",
      "tax incentives",
      "labour force"
    ],
    "answer": "balance of trade"
  },
  {
    "question": "Complete the sentence . The government is offering attractive …. to encourage foreign investment.",
    "options": [
      "exchange rate",
      "tax incentives",
      "foreign investment",
      "balance of trade",
      "inflation rate"
    ],
    "answer": "tax incentives"
  },
  {
    "question": "Complete the sentence. If you plan to borrow money, you will want to know the ……",
    "options": [
      "labour force",
      "government bureaucracy",
      "interest rate",
      "exchange rate",
      "unemployment rate"
    ],
    "answer": "interest rate"
  },
  {
    "question": "Complete the sentence. In countries where the …..is high, young people tend to study more.",
    "options": [
      "interest rate",
      "unemployment rate",
      "balance of trade",
      "government bureaucracy",
      "exchange rate"
    ],
    "answer": "unemployment rate"
  },
  {
    "question": "Complete the sentence. How many yen to the euro? Do you know the ……, by any chance?",
    "options": [
      "labour force",
      "exchange rate",
      "GDP(gross domestic product)",
      "interest rate",
      "inflation rate"
    ],
    "answer": "exchange rate"
  },
  {
    "question": "Complete the sentence. According to a recent survey, 12 per cent of the …..are earning less than the minimum wage.",
    "options": [
      "foreign investment",
      "labour force",
      "unemployment rate",
      "exchange rate",
      "government bureaucracy"
    ],
    "answer": "labour force"
  },
  {
    "question": "Match the word combination to its definition. A series of levels or steps in you working life.",
    "options": [
      "career break",
      "career ladder",
      "career plan",
      "career path",
      "career move"
    ],
    "answer": "career ladder"
  },
  {
    "question": "Match the word combination to its definition. The direction of your working life takes.",
    "options": [
      "career break",
      "career path",
      "career ladder",
      "career plan",
      "career opportunities"
    ],
    "answer": "career path"
  },
  {
    "question": "Match the word combination to its definition. An action you take to progress in your career.",
    "options": [
      "career break",
      "career move",
      "career plan",
      "career path",
      "career opportunities"
    ],
    "answer": "career move"
  },
  {
    "question": "Match the word combination to its definition. A period of time away from your job to, for example, look after your children.",
    "options": [
      "career move",
      "career break",
      "career path",
      "career plan",
      "career opportunities"
    ],
    "answer": "career break"
  },
  {
    "question": "Complete the sentence: In banking, you can .... with the big bonuses and retire at 35.",
    "options": [
      "earn commission",
      "make a fortune",
      "work flexitime",
      "get a promotion",
      "do part-time work"
    ],
    "answer": "make a fortune"
  },
  {
    "question": "Complete the sentence: When you ...., you can arrange your own schedule, so this is very convenient when you have",
    "options": [
      "make a fortune",
      "work flexitime",
      "do part-time work",
      "earn commission",
      "get a promotion"
    ],
    "answer": "work flexitime"
  },
  {
    "question": "Complete the sentence: People who work in sales often have the opportunity to ..... on top of a basic salary.",
    "options": [
      "work flexitime",
      "earn commission",
      "get a promotion",
      "make a fortune",
      "do part-time work"
    ],
    "answer": "earn commission"
  },
  {
    "question": "Complete the sentence: Luke is ambitious and does not want to be a sales assistant all his life. In fact, he hopes to ..... and",
    "options": [
      "do part-time work",
      "get a promotion",
      "earn commission",
      "work flexitime",
      "make a fortune"
    ],
    "answer": "get a promotion"
  },
  {
    "question": "Complete the sentence: Many students ..... when they are at university because it fits in with their studies.",
    "options": [
      "get a promotion",
      "do part-time work",
      "make a fortune",
      "earn commission",
      "work flexitime"
    ],
    "answer": "do part-time work"
  },
  {
    "question": "Complete the sentence: Employees in large multinationals ….. excellent career opportunities if they are willing to travel.",
    "options": [
      "climb",
      "have",
      "take",
      "decide",
      "offer"
    ],
    "answer": "have"
  },
  {
    "question": "Complete the sentence: Some people ….. a career break to do something adventurous like sailing round the world or going trekking in",
    "options": [
      "offer",
      "take",
      "climb",
      "have",
      "decide"
    ],
    "answer": "take"
  },
  {
    "question": "Complete the sentence: One way to ….. a career move is to join a small but rapidly growing company.",
    "options": [
      "climb",
      "make",
      "have",
      "offer",
      "take"
    ],
    "answer": "make"
  },
  {
    "question": "Complete the sentence: Certain companies ….. career opportunities to the long term unemployed or to people without formal",
    "options": [
      "climb",
      "offer",
      "take",
      "have",
      "make"
    ],
    "answer": "offer"
  },
  {
    "question": "Put the correct preposition. To be responsible …..",
    "options": [
      "at",
      "for",
      "with",
      "of",
      "that"
    ],
    "answer": "for"
  },
  {
    "question": "Put the correct preposition. To be in charge …..",
    "options": [
      "that",
      "of",
      "after",
      "for",
      "with"
    ],
    "answer": "of"
  },
  {
    "question": "Put the correct preposition. To deal …..",
    "options": [
      "after",
      "with",
      "for",
      "of",
      "that"
    ],
    "answer": "with"
  },
  {
    "question": "Complete the sentence: Jose Monzano is our security officer. He ….. that our staff and premises are protected against crime.",
    "options": [
      "deals",
      "makes sure",
      "involves",
      "is in charge",
      "looks"
    ],
    "answer": "makes sure"
  },
  {
    "question": "Complete the sentence: Hans Reiter is our new maintenance engineer. He checks all our equipment regularly and ….. of all repairs.",
    "options": [
      "deals",
      "is in charge",
      "looks",
      "involves",
      "makes sure"
    ],
    "answer": "is in charge"
  },
  {
    "question": "Complete the sentence: Linda Erikson is our Quality Control inspector. She ….. for monitoring our products and trying to improve their",
    "options": [
      "is in charge",
      "is responsible",
      "looks",
      "makes sure",
      "deals"
    ],
    "answer": "is responsible"
  },
  {
    "question": "Complete the sentence: Nadine works for HR. She ….. with staff problems, as well as with recruitment and training.",
    "options": [
      "makes sure",
      "deals",
      "looks",
      "involves",
      "to be in charge"
    ],
    "answer": "deals"
  },
  {
    "question": "Complete the sentence. So many forms to fill in just to import one photocopier! Nobody needs all this ……",
    "options": [
      "balance of trade",
      "government bureaucracy",
      "labour force",
      "GDP(gross domestic product)",
      "interest rate"
    ],
    "answer": "government bureaucracy"
  },
  {
    "question": "Complete the sentence. The higher the …..of a country, the richer its people are.",
    "options": [
      "inflation rate",
      "tax incentives",
      "unemployment rate",
      "labour force",
      "GDP(gross domestic product)"
    ],
    "answer": "GDP(gross domestic product)"
  },
  {
    "question": "Complete the sentence. When the value of a country`s exports is greater than the value of its imports, we say that the …….is favourable.",
    "options": [
      "inflation rate",
      "balance of trade",
      "interest rate",
      "unemployment rate",
      "GDP(gross domestic product)"
    ],
    "answer": "balance of trade"
  },
  {
    "question": "Complete the sentence. Prices increased again last month so the ……rose to 5.3 per cent.",
    "options": [
      "unemployment rate",
      "inflation rate",
      "GDP(gross domestic product)",
      "government bureaucracy",
      "exchange rate"
    ],
    "answer": "inflation rate"
  },
  {
    "question": "Match the economic term to its definition. The total amount of money spent by a government on schools, roads, the army, etc.",
    "options": [
      "foreign debt",
      "public expenditure",
      "subsidies",
      "trade deficit",
      "trade surplus"
    ],
    "answer": "public expenditure"
  },
  {
    "question": "Match the economic term to its definition. Money that a country owes to lenders abroad.",
    "options": [
      "GDP(gross domestic product)",
      "foreign debt",
      "balance of trade",
      "labour force",
      "subsidiary"
    ],
    "answer": "foreign debt"
  },
  {
    "question": "Match the economic term to its definition. Situation when a country sells more goods to other countries than it buys from other",
    "options": [
      "GDP(gross domestic product)",
      "trade surplus",
      "exchange rate",
      "interest rate",
      "tax incentives"
    ],
    "answer": "trade surplus"
  },
  {
    "question": "Match the economic term to its definition. Situation when a country pays more money for imports than it gets from exports.",
    "options": [
      "labour force",
      "trade deficit",
      "exchange rate",
      "foreign investment",
      "tax incentives"
    ],
    "answer": "trade deficit"
  },
  {
    "question": "Match the economic term to its definition. Money that a government pays to make something cheaper to buy.",
    "options": [
      "government bureaucracy",
      "subsidies",
      "unemployment rate",
      "exchange rate",
      "interest rate"
    ],
    "answer": "subsidies"
  },
  {
    "question": "Match the economic term to its definition. A period when trade and business activity decreases.",
    "options": [
      "GDP(gross domestic product)",
      "recession",
      "subsidiary",
      "make a fortune",
      "share price"
    ],
    "answer": "recession"
  },
  {
    "question": "Complete the sentence. We can`t invest in that country until their economy…..stable.",
    "options": [
      "will be",
      "is",
      "have been",
      "was",
      "will have been"
    ],
    "answer": "is"
  },
  {
    "question": "Complete the sentence. We`ll phone you when the goods ….here.",
    "options": [
      "were",
      "will be",
      "will have been",
      "are",
      "have been"
    ],
    "answer": "are"
  },
  {
    "question": "Match the two parts of the dialogue. These figures need checking.",
    "options": [
      "Yes, If anybody phones while I`m out, tell them I`ll be back by 1.30.",
      "When you`ve typed them all up, we can check them together.",
      "No, never again. Certainly not until they apologise for their terrible mistakes.",
      "We don`t know yet. We`ll have more information after we`ve talked to the team leader.",
      "Yes, I have. I`d like to discuss it with you when you have a minute."
    ],
    "answer": "When you`ve typed them all up, we can check them together."
  },
  {
    "question": "Complete the sentence. She remembers …..she first started her business.",
    "options": [
      "as soon as",
      "when",
      "whom",
      "until",
      "what"
    ],
    "answer": "when"
  },
  {
    "question": "Complete the sentence. He looked at our business plan ….we were waiting.",
    "options": [
      "while",
      "who",
      "where",
      "whom",
      "what"
    ],
    "answer": "while"
  },
  {
    "question": "Complete the sentence.….. interest rates rise, the economy will slow down.",
    "options": [
      "until",
      "as soon as",
      "what",
      "where",
      "before"
    ],
    "answer": "as soon as"
  },
  {
    "question": "Complete the sentence. We’ll deliver … they pay their last bill.",
    "options": [
      "what",
      "as soon as",
      "whom",
      "how",
      "where"
    ],
    "answer": "as soon as"
  },
  {
    "question": "Match the word to its definition. The rate at which money goes into a business.",
    "options": [
      "market share",
      "cash flow",
      "account",
      "salary",
      "deposit"
    ],
    "answer": "cash flow"
  },
  {
    "question": "Match the word to its definition. The difference between the money coming into and going out of a country.",
    "options": [
      "joint accounts",
      "balance of payments",
      "stock market",
      "key accounts",
      "trade surplus"
    ],
    "answer": "balance of payments"
  },
  {
    "question": "Complete the sentence: In some industries it can take a long time to ….. the career ladder.",
    "options": [
      "have",
      "climb",
      "make",
      "take",
      "offer"
    ],
    "answer": "climb"
  },
  {
    "question": "Choose the wrong noun phrase: make",
    "options": [
      "a mistake",
      "a training course",
      "a fortune",
      "a living",
      "progress"
    ],
    "answer": "a training course"
  },
  {
    "question": "Choose the wrong noun phrase: get",
    "options": [
      "the sack",
      "progress",
      "a promotion",
      "fired",
      "a bonus"
    ],
    "answer": "progress"
  },
  {
    "question": "Choose the wrong noun phrase: earn",
    "options": [
      "40 000 per year",
      "a part time job",
      "commission",
      "money",
      "a salary"
    ],
    "answer": "a part time job"
  },
  {
    "question": "Choose the wrong noun phrase: do",
    "options": [
      "part time work",
      "a mistake",
      "business",
      "a nine-to-five job",
      "your best"
    ],
    "answer": "a mistake"
  },
  {
    "question": "Choose the wrong noun phrase: take",
    "options": [
      "an opportunity",
      "a pension",
      "early retirement",
      "time off",
      "a chance"
    ],
    "answer": "a pension"
  },
  {
    "question": "Choose the wrong noun phrase: work",
    "options": [
      "flexitime",
      "an office job",
      "in shifts",
      "overtime",
      "anti-social hours"
    ],
    "answer": "an office job"
  },
  {
    "question": "Complete the sentence. .......... have been warned that their Facebook profile could damage their employment prospects.",
    "options": [
      "distraction",
      "jobseekers",
      "employment agency",
      "professional images",
      "candidate"
    ],
    "answer": "jobseekers"
  },
  {
    "question": "Choose the synonym of the word: charismatic",
    "options": [
      "stable",
      "organised",
      "serious",
      "attractive",
      "numerate"
    ],
    "answer": "attractive"
  },
  {
    "question": "Match the word to its definition. The difference between payments for imports and payments for exports.",
    "options": [
      "key accounts",
      "trade balance",
      "stock market",
      "joint accounts",
      "trade surplus"
    ],
    "answer": "trade balance"
  },
  {
    "question": "Complete the sentence: When a country exports more than it imports, it has a ….",
    "options": [
      "account balance",
      "trade surplus",
      "labour shortage",
      "income statement",
      "trade balance"
    ],
    "answer": "trade surplus"
  },
  {
    "question": "Complete the sentence. … we’ve finished the report, we’ll e-mail it to you.",
    "options": [
      "how",
      "when",
      "what",
      "where",
      "who"
    ],
    "answer": "when"
  },
  {
    "question": "Complete the sentence. … you fly first class, you get more leg room.",
    "options": [
      "whom",
      "when",
      "where",
      "what",
      "how"
    ],
    "answer": "when"
  },
  {
    "question": "Complete the sentence. … I’m in Geneva, I’ll review all the start-up costs.",
    "options": [
      "how",
      "when",
      "where",
      "what",
      "whom"
    ],
    "answer": "when"
  },
  {
    "question": "Complete the sentence. We won’t buy anything new … we’ve paid of all our debts.",
    "options": [
      "when",
      "until",
      "whom",
      "how",
      "who"
    ],
    "answer": "until"
  },
  {
    "question": "Complete the sentence. They'll start the meeting …. the manager arrives.",
    "options": [
      "how",
      "as soon as",
      "what",
      "where",
      "whom"
    ],
    "answer": "as soon as"
  },
  {
    "question": "Complete the sentence. I was finishing the report. …..my boss went out with clients.",
    "options": [
      "how",
      "when",
      "whom",
      "what",
      "where"
    ],
    "answer": "when"
  },
  {
    "question": "Complete the sentence. It's urgent, so I'll phone you ….. I get home.",
    "options": [
      "how",
      "as soon as",
      "whom",
      "what",
      "where"
    ],
    "answer": "as soon as"
  },
  {
    "question": "Complete the sentence. Can you check the figures …..you go home?",
    "options": [
      "what",
      "before",
      "who",
      "how",
      "where"
    ],
    "answer": "before"
  },
  {
    "question": "Match the sentence halves. Could you check the departure time …….",
    "options": [
      "when she finds a good job.",
      "before we leave for the airport.",
      "until the meeting has finished.",
      "the economy will slow down.",
      "as soon as you get to the office."
    ],
    "answer": "before we leave for the airport."
  },
  {
    "question": "Match the sentence halves. As soon as interest rates rise, ……..",
    "options": [
      "while you are still working.",
      "the economy will slow down.",
      "until we've saved enough money.",
      "before we leave for the airport.",
      "until the meeting has finished."
    ],
    "answer": "the economy will slow down."
  },
  {
    "question": "Match the sentence halves. We need to stay …………",
    "options": [
      "when she finds a good job.",
      "as soon as you get to the office.",
      "until the meeting has finished.",
      "before we leave for the airport.",
      "the economy will slow down."
    ],
    "answer": "until the meeting has finished."
  },
  {
    "question": "Match the sentence halves. The Finance Director needs to speak to you ……",
    "options": [
      "when the conditions are right.",
      "as soon as you get to the office.",
      "when she finds a good job.",
      "while you are still working.",
      "until we've saved enough money."
    ],
    "answer": "as soon as you get to the office."
  },
  {
    "question": "Match the sentence halves. She will move to Frankfurt ……..",
    "options": [
      "the economy will slow down.",
      "when she finds a good job.",
      "as soon as you get to the office.",
      "before we leave for the airport.",
      "until the meeting has finished."
    ],
    "answer": "when she finds a good job."
  },
  {
    "question": "Match the sentence halves. We won't open our new office …….",
    "options": [
      "while you are still working.",
      "until we've saved enough money.",
      "until the meeting has finished.",
      "the economy will slow down.",
      "when the conditions are right."
    ],
    "answer": "until we've saved enough money."
  },
  {
    "question": "Match the sentence halves. I think you should save some money ……..",
    "options": [
      "when she finds a good job.",
      "while you are still working.",
      "when the conditions are right.",
      "before we leave for the airport.",
      "until we've saved enough money."
    ],
    "answer": "while you are still working."
  },
  {
    "question": "Match the sentence halves. We can set up in that country ……..",
    "options": [
      "as soon as you get to the office.",
      "when the conditions are right.",
      "the economy will slow down.",
      "until the meeting has finished.",
      "while you are still working."
    ],
    "answer": "when the conditions are right."
  },
  {
    "question": "Match the government measure with its purpose. Create free training programmes",
    "options": [
      "improve the balance of trade",
      "reduce unemployment",
      "stimulate consumer spending",
      "stop companies polluting the air and water",
      "reduce the budget"
    ],
    "answer": "reduce unemployment"
  },
  {
    "question": "Match the government measure with its purpose. Make export easier",
    "options": [
      "make a breakthrough",
      "improve the balance of trade",
      "stop companies polluting the air and water",
      "reduce the budget",
      "win an award"
    ],
    "answer": "improve the balance of trade"
  },
  {
    "question": "Match the government measure with its purpose. Pass a very strict environmental law",
    "options": [
      "reduce unemployment",
      "stop companies polluting the air and water",
      "reduce the budget deficit",
      "attract foreign investors",
      "stimulate consumer spending"
    ],
    "answer": "stop companies polluting the air and water"
  },
  {
    "question": "Choose the right conjunction. We were unable to finance the new project ……severe cashflow problems.",
    "options": [
      "so",
      "because of",
      "though",
      "because",
      "as"
    ],
    "answer": "because of"
  },
  {
    "question": "Match the government measure with its purpose. Raise taxes",
    "options": [
      "stimulate consumers",
      "reduce the budget deficit",
      "balance of trade",
      "stop companies polluting the air and water",
      "reduce unemployment"
    ],
    "answer": "reduce the budget deficit"
  },
  {
    "question": "Match the government measure with its purpose. Lower the interest rate",
    "options": [
      "meet a need",
      "stimulate consumer spending",
      "make a breakthrough",
      "stop companies polluting the air and water",
      "enter a market"
    ],
    "answer": "stimulate consumer spending"
  },
  {
    "question": "Match the government measure with its purpose. Reduce bureaucracy",
    "options": [
      "reduce the budget deficit",
      "attract foreign investors",
      "stop companies polluting the air and water",
      "improve the balance of trade",
      "stimulate consumer spending"
    ],
    "answer": "attract foreign investors"
  },
  {
    "question": "Match the word or word combination to its definition. A period when the economy is getting smaller because it is producing less.",
    "options": [
      "economic output",
      "trading",
      "breakthrough",
      "negative growth",
      "boom"
    ],
    "answer": "negative growth"
  },
  {
    "question": "Choose the opposite for the word: export",
    "options": [
      "import",
      "goods",
      "dispatch",
      "foreign trade",
      "foreign investment"
    ],
    "answer": "import"
  },
  {
    "question": "Match the word to its definition. A period when there is a negative growth.",
    "options": [
      "increase",
      "boom",
      "balance of trade",
      "recession",
      "trade surplus"
    ],
    "answer": "recession"
  },
  {
    "question": "Choose the synonym of the word: income",
    "options": [
      "promotion",
      "discount",
      "inflation rate",
      "profit",
      "stock"
    ],
    "answer": "profit"
  },
  {
    "question": "Complete the sentence. In terms of jobs, the… continues to be a problem, as it is still 16%.",
    "options": [
      "foreign debt",
      "GDP(gross domestic product)",
      "bureaucracy",
      "exchange rate",
      "unemployment rate"
    ],
    "answer": "unemployment rate"
  },
  {
    "question": "Complete the sentence: A large skilled means there could be attractive investment opportunities over the next five years.",
    "options": [
      "buyers",
      "subsidiaries",
      "parent companies",
      "labour force",
      "workload"
    ],
    "answer": "labour force"
  },
  {
    "question": "Choose the synonym of the word: jobless",
    "options": [
      "customers",
      "traders",
      "employers",
      "shareholders",
      "unemployed"
    ],
    "answer": "unemployed"
  },
  {
    "question": "Match the sentence to a suitable ending. An Australian entrepreneur expressed interest in the new product….",
    "options": [
      "when they saw an opening in the market.",
      "when suddenly Jackson announced that he was stepping down as General Manager.",
      "and asked them to talk about innovation and change.",
      "that they were exhibiting at the Inventors` Fair.",
      "and sold 3 million of the devices in 80 days."
    ],
    "answer": "that they were exhibiting at the Inventors` Fair."
  },
  {
    "question": "Match the word partnership to its definition. The way that companies in general behave, the way business is done in a particular place.",
    "options": [
      "long-hours culture",
      "sales culture",
      "corporate culture",
      "business culture",
      "culture shock"
    ],
    "answer": "business culture"
  },
  {
    "question": "Choose the synonym of the word: holiday",
    "options": [
      "peak",
      "extension",
      "target",
      "goal",
      "vacation"
    ],
    "answer": "vacation"
  },
  {
    "question": "Match the word to its definition. A movement or position of the hand, arm, body, head, or face to express an idea, emotion.",
    "options": [
      "skill",
      "extension",
      "gesture",
      "order",
      "recession"
    ],
    "answer": "gesture"
  },
  {
    "question": "Match the word to its definition. The quality of being funny.",
    "options": [
      "gesture",
      "distance",
      "humour",
      "pleasure",
      "extension"
    ],
    "answer": "humour"
  },
  {
    "question": "Choose the right prepositions: A company's culture depends…...a large extent…...the country it is based….....",
    "options": [
      "on, in, -",
      "to, -, in",
      "at, in, on",
      "from, in,of",
      "to, on, in"
    ],
    "answer": "to, on, in"
  },
  {
    "question": "Complete the sentence. Jane invited me round for dinner last night. Her husband is a wonderful ……..",
    "options": [
      "cookies",
      "cooker",
      "cuisine",
      "dishing",
      "cook"
    ],
    "answer": "cook"
  },
  {
    "question": "Choose the right prepositions. I look forward…hearing…you.",
    "options": [
      "for, on",
      "from, at",
      "about, of",
      "to, from",
      "at, in"
    ],
    "answer": "to, from"
  },
  {
    "question": "Form the word partnerships: 1) convenient; 2) local; 3) efficient a) food; b) service; c) location",
    "options": [
      "1-a; 2-b;3-c",
      "1-b; 2-a; 3-c",
      "1-b; 2-c; 3-a",
      "1-c; 2-a; 3-b",
      "1-c; 2-b; 3-a"
    ],
    "answer": "1-c; 2-a; 3-b"
  },
  {
    "question": "Form the word partnerships: 1) cosy; 2) local; 3) reasonablea) prices; b) atmosphere;c) entertainment",
    "options": [
      "1-a; 2-c; 3-b",
      "1-b; 2-a; 3-c",
      "1-a; 2-b; 3-c",
      "1-c; 2-b; 3-a",
      "1-b; 2-c;3-a"
    ],
    "answer": "1-b; 2-c;3-a"
  },
  {
    "question": "Find the extra word:",
    "options": [
      "venison",
      "pork",
      "lamb",
      "veal",
      "cabbage"
    ],
    "answer": "cabbage"
  },
  {
    "question": "Find the extra word:",
    "options": [
      "lamb",
      "cabbage",
      "cucumber",
      "onion",
      "spinach"
    ],
    "answer": "lamb"
  },
  {
    "question": "Find the extra word:",
    "options": [
      "crab",
      "lobster",
      "tuna",
      "chicken",
      "salmon"
    ],
    "answer": "chicken"
  },
  {
    "question": "Complete the sentence: Many people have only two ….a day: breakfast and dinner.",
    "options": [
      "cooks",
      "dishes",
      "cuisine",
      "courses",
      "meals"
    ],
    "answer": "meals"
  },
  {
    "question": "Complete the sentence: Tom worked in Bangkok for a year and now he is very keen on Thai…..",
    "options": [
      "kitchen",
      "dish",
      "dishing",
      "cuisine",
      "cooker"
    ],
    "answer": "cuisine"
  },
  {
    "question": "Complete the sentence: They are vegetarians so we should not buy any ….",
    "options": [
      "meal",
      "food",
      "spinach",
      "meat",
      "onion"
    ],
    "answer": "meat"
  },
  {
    "question": "Complete the sentence: This chocolate mousse is delicious. Could I have the ….?",
    "options": [
      "receipt",
      "recipe",
      "cuisine",
      "cookbook",
      "cooker"
    ],
    "answer": "recipe"
  },
  {
    "question": "Match the sentence halves. Last week, I had to look……",
    "options": [
      "to a very good restaurant.",
      "after five clients from Turkey.",
      "on really well.",
      "up their invitation next summer.",
      "come over and see them in Antalya."
    ],
    "answer": "after five clients from Turkey."
  },
  {
    "question": "Match the sentence halves. First, I showed them around ………",
    "options": [
      "after five clients from Turkey.",
      "the Old Town.",
      "to seeing them all again.",
      "up their invitation next summer.",
      "on really well."
    ],
    "answer": "the Old Town."
  },
  {
    "question": "Match the sentence halves. I certainly look forward…….",
    "options": [
      "up their invitation next summer.",
      "to seeing them all again.",
      "to a very good restaurant.",
      "come over and see them in Antalya.",
      "the Old Town."
    ],
    "answer": "to seeing them all again."
  },
  {
    "question": "Match the sentence halves. I hope I can take ……",
    "options": [
      "to seeing them all again.",
      "up their invitation next summer.",
      "come over and see them in Antalya.",
      "after five clients from Turkey.",
      "on really well."
    ],
    "answer": "up their invitation next summer."
  },
  {
    "question": "Match the sentence halves. One of them did not turn ……",
    "options": [
      "on really well.",
      "up, unfortunately.",
      "up their invitation next summer.",
      "to a very good restaurant.",
      "after five clients from Turkey."
    ],
    "answer": "up, unfortunately."
  },
  {
    "question": "Match the sentence halves. The food was delicious and we all got …….",
    "options": [
      "to seeing them all again.",
      "on really well.",
      "to a very good restaurant.",
      "up their invitation next summer.",
      "come over and see them in Antalya."
    ],
    "answer": "on really well."
  },
  {
    "question": "Match the sentence halves. Then, I took them out……..",
    "options": [
      "after five clients from Turkey.",
      "to a very good restaurant.",
      "on really well.",
      "come over and see them in Antalya.",
      "entertaining"
    ],
    "answer": "to a very good restaurant."
  },
  {
    "question": "Match the sentence halves. They said I should …….",
    "options": [
      "the Old Town.",
      "come over and see them in Antalya.",
      "up their invitation next summer.",
      "to seeing them all again.",
      "after five clients from Turkey."
    ],
    "answer": "come over and see them in Antalya."
  },
  {
    "question": "Choose the right prepositions. We looked …the lunch menu, which had a wide variety …typical dishes …our region.",
    "options": [
      "in, from, of",
      "at, of, from",
      "on, with, from",
      "at, in, of",
      "of, from, of"
    ],
    "answer": "at, of, from"
  },
  {
    "question": "Use the explanation to choose the correct verb. Rick thought March was too early for our seminar so he …..it ….until May. (arranged to",
    "options": [
      "hold on",
      "came up with",
      "carrying out",
      "put off",
      "set up"
    ],
    "answer": "put off"
  },
  {
    "question": "Use the explanation to choose the correct verb. Unfortunately, we had to ….their invitation because we had another engagement.",
    "options": [
      "look after",
      "turn down",
      "carrying out",
      "hold on",
      "looked for"
    ],
    "answer": "turn down"
  },
  {
    "question": "Match the sentence to a suitable ending. Could you book one single room…..",
    "options": [
      "so not too expensive?",
      "in the name of Robert Dorey.",
      "and leaving on the 7th in the morning.",
      "it`s too far from the centre.",
      "a non-smoking room."
    ],
    "answer": "in the name of Robert Dorey."
  },
  {
    "question": "Match the sentence to a suitable ending. If possible, he would prefer …...",
    "options": [
      "and leaving on the 7th in the morning.",
      "a non-smoking room.",
      "it`s too far from the centre.",
      "in the name of Robert Dorey.",
      "but not too expensive?"
    ],
    "answer": "a non-smoking room."
  },
  {
    "question": "Match the multiword verb with its definition. Who's going to /look after/ our guests tonight?",
    "options": [
      "await with pleasure",
      "take care of",
      "entertain",
      "accept",
      "get involved in"
    ],
    "answer": "take care of"
  },
  {
    "question": "Match the multiword verb with its definition. We have two hours to /look around/ the city.",
    "options": [
      "arrive",
      "see the sights",
      "get involved in",
      "await with pleasure",
      "take care of"
    ],
    "answer": "see the sights"
  },
  {
    "question": "Match the multiword verb with its definition. We're really /looking forward/ to the Tokyo trip.",
    "options": [
      "arrive",
      "await with pleasure",
      "refuse",
      "see the sights",
      "entertain"
    ],
    "answer": "await with pleasure"
  },
  {
    "question": "Match the multiword verb with its definition. Let's /take the clients out/ to a Chinese restaurant.",
    "options": [
      "take care of",
      "entertain",
      "see the sights",
      "refuse",
      "get involved in"
    ],
    "answer": "entertain"
  },
  {
    "question": "Match the multiword verb with its definition. Seventy staff /took part/ in our fundraising events.",
    "options": [
      "entertain",
      "get involved in",
      "refuse",
      "take care of",
      "accept"
    ],
    "answer": "get involved in"
  },
  {
    "question": "Match the multiword verb with its definition. The CEO would like to /take up/ your kind offer.",
    "options": [
      "arrive",
      "accept",
      "await with pleasure",
      "see the sights",
      "refuse"
    ],
    "answer": "accept"
  },
  {
    "question": "Match the multiword verb with its definition. We were delighted that so many sponsors /turned up/ at the event.",
    "options": [
      "accept",
      "arrive",
      "await with pleasure",
      "get involved in",
      "take care of"
    ],
    "answer": "arrive"
  },
  {
    "question": "Match the multiword verb with its definition. As we had another engagement, we had to /turn down/ their invitation.",
    "options": [
      "take care of",
      "refuse",
      "entertain",
      "accept",
      "see the sights"
    ],
    "answer": "refuse"
  },
  {
    "question": "Make up the sentence: afraid/ I/ missed/ your/ I`m/ the/ company/ of/ name",
    "options": [
      "Your name I missed the company I`m afraid of.",
      "I'm afraid I missed the name of your company.",
      "I`m missed of the company I afraid your name.",
      "I missed afraid the company of your I`m name.",
      "I afraid the name of your company I`m missed."
    ],
    "answer": "I'm afraid I missed the name of your company."
  },
  {
    "question": "Make up the sentence: you/ Would/ dinner/ with/ like/ us/ tomorrow/ to/ night/ have?",
    "options": [
      "Would us have you like tomorrow with dinner night to?",
      "Would dinner like to us with night tomorrow have you?",
      "Would you like to have dinner with us tomorrow night?",
      "Would you have to night dinner with us tomorrow like?",
      "Would you have with tomorrow dinner like to night us?"
    ],
    "answer": "Would you like to have dinner with us tomorrow night?"
  },
  {
    "question": "Match the word combination to its definition. To organize a meeting.",
    "options": [
      "to run a meeting",
      "to set up a meeting",
      "to bring forward a meeting",
      "to put back a meeting",
      "to call off a meeting"
    ],
    "answer": "to set up a meeting"
  },
  {
    "question": "Choose the synonym of the word: put back",
    "options": [
      "arrange",
      "put off",
      "use",
      "decide",
      "launched"
    ],
    "answer": "put off"
  },
  {
    "question": "Choose the synonym of the word: put off",
    "options": [
      "start",
      "postpone",
      "plan",
      "behave",
      "compete"
    ],
    "answer": "postpone"
  },
  {
    "question": "Complete the sentence: Susana is the receptionist. She ….. after visitors and takes messages.",
    "options": [
      "is in charge",
      "looks",
      "involves",
      "deals",
      "makes sure"
    ],
    "answer": "looks"
  },
  {
    "question": "Match the word or word combination to its definition. The way the presenter looks at the audience.",
    "options": [
      "physical contact",
      "eye contact",
      "touch",
      "breakdown",
      "gesture"
    ],
    "answer": "eye contact"
  },
  {
    "question": "Complete the sentence. Maintain …. by looking round the room at each person in the audience for about a second.",
    "options": [
      "booking",
      "eye contact",
      "attachment",
      "friendship",
      "gestures"
    ],
    "answer": "eye contact"
  },
  {
    "question": "Complete the sentence. Use …… - hand movements - to emphasise key points.",
    "options": [
      "humour",
      "gesture",
      "distance",
      "booking",
      "eye contact"
    ],
    "answer": "gesture"
  },
  {
    "question": "Match the word or phrase to its definition. The way you hold your body, the gestures you make, etc.",
    "options": [
      "loyalty",
      "body language",
      "physical contact",
      "hierarchy",
      "role of silence"
    ],
    "answer": "body language"
  },
  {
    "question": "Match the word or phrase to its definition. The degree to which it`s acceptable to touch someone`s shoulder.",
    "options": [
      "body language",
      "physical contact",
      "breakdown",
      "action point",
      "visual aids"
    ],
    "answer": "physical contact"
  },
  {
    "question": "Complete the sentence. Sales have fallen…in the last three years",
    "options": [
      "best",
      "sharply",
      "slight",
      "calm",
      "hard"
    ],
    "answer": "sharply"
  },
  {
    "question": "Complete the sentence: Pollution is a big problem in our city and we are trying all sorts of ideas to … it.",
    "options": [
      "increase",
      "reduce",
      "do",
      "deliver",
      "rise"
    ],
    "answer": "reduce"
  },
  {
    "question": "Complete the phrase with the correct verb: …to the dentist",
    "options": [
      "waiting",
      "going",
      "making",
      "finding",
      "taking"
    ],
    "answer": "going"
  },
  {
    "question": "Complete the phrase with the correct verb: …in a long queue",
    "options": [
      "travelling",
      "waiting",
      "going",
      "having",
      "taking"
    ],
    "answer": "waiting"
  },
  {
    "question": "Complete the phrase with the correct verb: …stuck in a traffic jam",
    "options": [
      "making",
      "being",
      "going",
      "travelling",
      "finding"
    ],
    "answer": "being"
  },
  {
    "question": "Complete the phrase with the correct verb: …a parking space",
    "options": [
      "waiting",
      "finding",
      "shopping",
      "going",
      "travelling"
    ],
    "answer": "finding"
  },
  {
    "question": "Complete the phrase with the correct verb: …an interview",
    "options": [
      "shopping",
      "having",
      "being",
      "travelling",
      "waiting"
    ],
    "answer": "having"
  },
  {
    "question": "Complete the phrase with the correct verb: …a speech",
    "options": [
      "shopping",
      "making",
      "waiting",
      "going",
      "travelling"
    ],
    "answer": "making"
  },
  {
    "question": "Complete the phrase with the correct verb: …by air",
    "options": [
      "waiting",
      "travelling",
      "finding",
      "having",
      "shopping"
    ],
    "answer": "travelling"
  },
  {
    "question": "Match the word or word combination to its definition. A system where employees choose the time they start and finish work each day.",
    "options": [
      "workload",
      "flexitime",
      "working environment",
      "deadline",
      "workaholic"
    ],
    "answer": "flexitime"
  },
  {
    "question": "Match the word or word combination to its definition. A time or date by which you have to do something",
    "options": [
      "flexitime",
      "deadline",
      "working environment",
      "workaholic",
      "lifestyle"
    ],
    "answer": "deadline"
  },
  {
    "question": "Match the word or word combination to its definition. How personally satisfied you are with the way you live and work.",
    "options": [
      "workload",
      "quality of life",
      "flexitime",
      "lifestyle",
      "working environment"
    ],
    "answer": "quality of life"
  },
  {
    "question": "Match the word or word combination to its definition. Someone who cannot stop working and has no time for anything else.",
    "options": [
      "flexitime",
      "workaholic",
      "working environment",
      "lifestyle",
      "deadline"
    ],
    "answer": "workaholic"
  },
  {
    "question": "Match the word or word combination to its definition. The ability to give a good amount of time to your work and to outside interests,",
    "options": [
      "deadline",
      "work-life balance",
      "workload",
      "workaholic",
      "flexitime"
    ],
    "answer": "work-life balance"
  },
  {
    "question": "Match the word or word combination to its definition. The amount of work a person is expected to do.",
    "options": [
      "deadline",
      "workload",
      "flexitime",
      "workaholic",
      "working environment"
    ],
    "answer": "workload"
  },
  {
    "question": "Match the word or word combination to its definition. The people, things and atmosphere around you at work.",
    "options": [
      "lifestyle",
      "flexitime",
      "quality of life",
      "workload",
      "working environment"
    ],
    "answer": "working environment"
  },
  {
    "question": "Match the word or word combination to its definition. The way people choose to organise their lives.",
    "options": [
      "deadline",
      "lifestyle",
      "working environment",
      "workload",
      "workaholic"
    ],
    "answer": "lifestyle"
  },
  {
    "question": "Complete the sentence with an appropriate word. I work six days a week and never have a holiday. My girlfriend says I'm a ............",
    "options": [
      "speculator",
      "workaholic",
      "energetic",
      "visionary",
      "workload"
    ],
    "answer": "workaholic"
  },
  {
    "question": "Complete the sentence with an appropriate word or phrase. I worked until 11 o'clock at night to meet the….. for presenting the",
    "options": [
      "flexitime",
      "deadline",
      "lifestyle",
      "working environment",
      "workload"
    ],
    "answer": "deadline"
  },
  {
    "question": "Make up the sentence: working/ computer/ I/ my/ properly/ replied/ wasn`t.",
    "options": [
      "I replied my properly wasn`t computer working.",
      "I replied my computer wasn`t working properly.",
      "I properly working wasn`t computer my working.",
      "I working my replied computer wasn`t properly.",
      "I wasn`t computer properly my replied working."
    ],
    "answer": "I replied my computer wasn`t working properly."
  },
  {
    "question": "Make up the sentence: a/ He/ I/ needed/ new/ one/ said/ that.",
    "options": [
      "He said I needed that one a new.",
      "He said that I needed a new one.",
      "He said a new one needed that I.",
      "He new a said that needed I one.",
      "He needed I said a new one that."
    ],
    "answer": "He said that I needed a new one."
  },
  {
    "question": "Make up the sentence: ahead/ to/ Then/ he/ should/ plan/ said/ try/ I.",
    "options": [
      "Then I said to should try he ahead plan.",
      "Then he said I should try to plan ahead.",
      "Then I plan should to try said he ahead.",
      "Then I should to try ahead said he plan.",
      "Then he plan should try to said I ahead."
    ],
    "answer": "Then he said I should try to plan ahead."
  },
  {
    "question": "Complete the sentence with an appropriate word or phrase. Karl has a heavy ….. at the moment because several colleagues are off",
    "options": [
      "deadline",
      "workload",
      "landline",
      "flexitime",
      "distance"
    ],
    "answer": "workload"
  },
  {
    "question": "Complete the sentence with an appropriate word or phrase. A clean, quiet, comfortable and friendly ….can actively reduce levels of",
    "options": [
      "workload",
      "working environment",
      "discount",
      "distance",
      "deadline"
    ],
    "answer": "working environment"
  },
  {
    "question": "Make up the sentence: are only/ at work/ many men/ under pressure/ by contrast,",
    "options": [
      "Many men are only at work by contrast, under pressure.",
      "By contrast, many men are only under pressure at work.",
      "Under pressure many men by contrast, are only at work.",
      "At work by contrast, many men under pressure are only.",
      "Many men under pressure by contrast, are only at work."
    ],
    "answer": "By contrast, many men are only under pressure at work."
  },
  {
    "question": "Make up the sentence: come from/ from work/ home and/ These pressures",
    "options": [
      "Come from these pressures from work home and.",
      "These pressures come from home and from work.",
      "From work come from these pressures home and.",
      "Home and from work these pressures come from.",
      "These pressures home and come from from work."
    ],
    "answer": "These pressures come from home and from work."
  },
  {
    "question": "Make up the sentence: handle stress/ but men and/ very differently/ women generally",
    "options": [
      "Very differently handle stress but men and women generally.",
      "But men and women generally handle stress very differently.",
      "Handle stress women generally but men and very differently.",
      "Women generally very differently handle stress but men and.",
      "But men and very different handle stress women generally."
    ],
    "answer": "But men and women generally handle stress very differently."
  },
  {
    "question": "Choose the right prepositions. Being stuck…a traffic jam on your way…work can be quite stressful.",
    "options": [
      "on, for",
      "of, about",
      "to, on",
      "in, to",
      "for, on"
    ],
    "answer": "in, to"
  },
  {
    "question": "Choose the right prepositions. In Ireland,... example, the economy is shrinking and business owners are worried ….how they will keep",
    "options": [
      "for, about",
      "of, on",
      "on, for",
      "in, at",
      "to, on"
    ],
    "answer": "for, about"
  },
  {
    "question": "Choose the right prepositions. Gentaro is part …a multinational company based… Milan.",
    "options": [
      "on, on",
      "of, in",
      "of, at",
      "in, to",
      "for, on"
    ],
    "answer": "of, in"
  },
  {
    "question": "Choose the right prepositions. I wish I could relax a bit more instead … having to work… strict deadlines all the time.",
    "options": [
      "on, for",
      "of, to",
      "with, on",
      "in, at",
      "for, on"
    ],
    "answer": "of, to"
  },
  {
    "question": "Choose the right prepositions. Lisa worked until 11 o`clock … night to meet the deadline … presenting the report.",
    "options": [
      "on, of",
      "at, for",
      "of, for",
      "in, to",
      "at, in"
    ],
    "answer": "at, for"
  },
  {
    "question": "Choose the right prepositions. Mike says going… a stress counsellor is out… the question.",
    "options": [
      "on, in",
      "to, of",
      "for, to",
      "in, on",
      "at, in"
    ],
    "answer": "to, of"
  },
  {
    "question": "Choose the right preposition. The finance sector changed dramatically…. the past five years.",
    "options": [
      "about",
      "over",
      "at",
      "for",
      "out"
    ],
    "answer": "over"
  },
  {
    "question": "Choose the right preposition. Stress levels have increased…. recent years.",
    "options": [
      "at",
      "on",
      "to",
      "in",
      "of"
    ],
    "answer": "in"
  },
  {
    "question": "Choose the right preposition. Many employees worry…. the future.",
    "options": [
      "since",
      "about",
      "under",
      "in",
      "at"
    ],
    "answer": "about"
  },
  {
    "question": "Use the explanation to choose the correct verb. We …..a new sales manager with at least three years` experience. (tried to find)",
    "options": [
      "hold on",
      "looked for",
      "set up",
      "put off",
      "turn down"
    ],
    "answer": "looked for"
  },
  {
    "question": "Use the explanation to choose the correct verb. Carol …..a well-paid job to train as a social worker. (stopped doing)",
    "options": [
      "came up with",
      "gave up",
      "put off",
      "hold on",
      "set up"
    ],
    "answer": "gave up"
  },
  {
    "question": "Choose the synonym of the word: challenging",
    "options": [
      "professional",
      "difficult",
      "steady",
      "environmental",
      "following"
    ],
    "answer": "difficult"
  },
  {
    "question": "Complete the sentence: He`s completely …. - so stressed and tired by his work that he will never be able to work again.",
    "options": [
      "patient",
      "burned out",
      "calm",
      "tiring",
      "energetic"
    ],
    "answer": "burned out"
  },
  {
    "question": "Make up the sentence: organised/ was/ answered/ well/ I/ usually/ I/ that.",
    "options": [
      "I usually well answered that was I organised.",
      "I answered that I was usually well organised.",
      "I was well that usually I organised answered.",
      "I was that answered well I usually organised.",
      "I organised was that usually I answered well."
    ],
    "answer": "I answered that I was usually well organised."
  },
  {
    "question": "Make up the sentence: a/ asked/ computer/ Finally,/ get/ him/ I/ I/ new/ when/ would.",
    "options": [
      "Finally, a new I asked would computer I get him when.",
      "Finally, I would him asked computer I when a new get.",
      "Finally, when I asked would a computer I new get him.",
      "Finally, I asked him when I would get a new computer.",
      "Finally, would him a new asked I computer get when I."
    ],
    "answer": "Finally, I asked him when I would get a new computer."
  },
  {
    "question": "Choose the right preposition: He asked her if she adapted easily …new situation.",
    "options": [
      "by",
      "to",
      "of",
      "on",
      "from"
    ],
    "answer": "to"
  },
  {
    "question": "Choose the right preposition: He asked her how often she invested …courses.",
    "options": [
      "about",
      "in",
      "by",
      "at",
      "of"
    ],
    "answer": "in"
  },
  {
    "question": "Complete the sentence. He likes people to feel comfortable and relaxed during a negotiation. He's a very…… person.",
    "options": [
      "enthusiasm",
      "calm",
      "creative",
      "intelligent",
      "ambitious"
    ],
    "answer": "calm"
  },
  {
    "question": "Complete the sentence. She never talks about her achievements. She is so ……..",
    "options": [
      "creative",
      "modest",
      "enthusiastic",
      "numerate",
      "unfriendly"
    ],
    "answer": "modest"
  },
  {
    "question": "Complete the sentence. She is very ….. She wants to be more successful than other people.",
    "options": [
      "ambition",
      "competitive",
      "modest",
      "impatient",
      "creative"
    ],
    "answer": "competitive"
  },
  {
    "question": "Complete the sentence. It was very impolite to be late for the meeting and not even.......",
    "options": [
      "formal",
      "apologise",
      "help",
      "respond",
      "say"
    ],
    "answer": "apologise"
  },
  {
    "question": "Complete the sentence: She believes that the new director should involve staff in all ….......",
    "options": [
      "decisive",
      "decisions",
      "workaholic",
      "interviews",
      "employment"
    ],
    "answer": "decisions"
  },
  {
    "question": "Complete the sentence: However, some critics argue that introducing professionals would help ….. a reputation for weak",
    "options": [
      "spread",
      "to break down",
      "influenced",
      "increase",
      "generate"
    ],
    "answer": "to break down"
  },
  {
    "question": "Choose the synonym of the word: seriousness",
    "options": [
      "network",
      "formality",
      "relation",
      "document",
      "reply"
    ],
    "answer": "formality"
  },
  {
    "question": "Choose the synonym of the word: significantly",
    "options": [
      "annually",
      "importantly",
      "recently",
      "slightly",
      "lately"
    ],
    "answer": "importantly"
  },
  {
    "question": "Choose the synonym of the word: qualifications",
    "options": [
      "breakthrough",
      "background",
      "refund",
      "range",
      "recession"
    ],
    "answer": "background"
  },
  {
    "question": "Choose the right prepositions. I am available … interview …the date that you mention.",
    "options": [
      "from, of",
      "for, on",
      "in, at",
      "on, from",
      "about, in"
    ],
    "answer": "for, on"
  },
  {
    "question": "Match the two parts of the dialogue. It seems we`re not doing business with Alfatex anymore.",
    "options": [
      "When you`ve typed them all up, we can check them together.",
      "Yes, I agree. We`ll find out as soon as we get the FT.",
      "No, never again. Certainly not until they apologise for their terrible mistakes.",
      "Yes, If anybody phones while I`m out, tell them I`ll be back by 1.30.",
      "Well, could we possibly do that before the meeting starts?"
    ],
    "answer": "No, never again. Certainly not until they apologise for their terrible mistakes."
  },
  {
    "question": "Match the two parts of the dialogue. It would be useful to know today`s exchange rates.",
    "options": [
      "Yes, If anybody phones while I`m out, tell them I`ll be back by 1.30.",
      "Yes, I agree. We`ll find out as soon as we get the FT.",
      "No, never again. Certainly not until they apologise for their terrible mistakes.",
      "When you`ve typed them all up, we can check them together.",
      "Well, could we possibly do that before the meeting starts?"
    ],
    "answer": "Yes, I agree. We`ll find out as soon as we get the FT."
  },
  {
    "question": "Complete the sentence: Some staff feel…... and are not valued by management.",
    "options": [
      "respected",
      "worthless",
      "stress",
      "nervous",
      "valuable"
    ],
    "answer": "worthless"
  },
  {
    "question": "Choose the right conjunction. Sales are falling ….. management doesn’t seem very worried about it.",
    "options": [
      "because of",
      "but",
      "so",
      "as",
      "because"
    ],
    "answer": "but"
  },
  {
    "question": "Choose the synonym of the word: proposal",
    "options": [
      "attitude",
      "offer",
      "diary",
      "pressure",
      "stake"
    ],
    "answer": "offer"
  },
  {
    "question": "Complete the sentence. Countries at the top of the stress league are those where …., on average, take fewer holidays each year.",
    "options": [
      "commercials",
      "business owners",
      "international companies",
      "employment",
      "the rich"
    ],
    "answer": "business owners"
  },
  {
    "question": "Complete the sentence: Business owners were asked about the major causes of…stress.",
    "options": [
      "balance of trade",
      "workplace",
      "workaholics",
      "sales",
      "career ladder"
    ],
    "answer": "workplace"
  },
  {
    "question": "Match the word partnership to its definition. All the great ideas are controversial",
    "options": [
      "close a deal",
      "causing disagreement",
      "compromise",
      "original",
      "reach an agreement"
    ],
    "answer": "causing disagreement"
  },
  {
    "question": "Match the word partnership to its definition. to take advantage of an opportunity",
    "options": [
      "to make an important discovery or change",
      "to do something when you get the chance to do it",
      "to offer a larger variety of goods",
      "to make somebody look or feel more important",
      "to do or provide something that is necessary"
    ],
    "answer": "to do something when you get the chance to do it"
  },
  {
    "question": "Match the word partnership to its definition. to enter a market",
    "options": [
      "to make an important discovery or change",
      "to start selling goods or services in a new area",
      "to do or provide something that is necessary",
      "to do something when you get the chance to do it",
      "to offer a larger variety of goods"
    ],
    "answer": "to start selling goods or services in a new area"
  },
  {
    "question": "Match the word partnership to its definition. to extend a product range",
    "options": [
      "to make an important discovery or change",
      "to offer a larger variety of goods",
      "to make somebody look or feel more important",
      "to do something when you get the chance to do it",
      "to start selling goods or services in a new area"
    ],
    "answer": "to offer a larger variety of goods"
  },
  {
    "question": "Match the word partnership to its definition. to make a breakthrough",
    "options": [
      "to start selling goods or services in a new area",
      "to make an important discovery or change",
      "to do something when you get the chance to do it",
      "to do or provide something that is necessary",
      "to make somebody look or feel more important"
    ],
    "answer": "to make an important discovery or change"
  },
  {
    "question": "Make up the sentence: repairing/ someone/ your/ now/ is/ machine/ washing.",
    "options": [
      "Now someone your repairing machine is washing.",
      "Someone is repairing your washing machine now.",
      "Machine is someone now repairing washing your.",
      "Washing machine is your someone now repairing.",
      "Your machine is washing now repairing someone."
    ],
    "answer": "Someone is repairing your washing machine now."
  },
  {
    "question": "Match the word partnership to its definition. to raise somebody's status",
    "options": [
      "to do or provide something that is necessary",
      "to make somebody look or feel more important",
      "to start selling goods or services in a new area",
      "to offer a larger variety of goods",
      "to do something when you get the chance to do it"
    ],
    "answer": "to make somebody look or feel more important"
  },
  {
    "question": "Match the word partnership to its definition. to meet a need",
    "options": [
      "to make an important discovery or change",
      "to do or provide something that is necessary",
      "to offer a larger variety of goods",
      "to do something when you get the chance to do it",
      "to make somebody look or feel more important"
    ],
    "answer": "to do or provide something that is necessary"
  },
  {
    "question": "Complete the sentence: We plan to offer free ice-cream to all consumers one day a year to … awareness of the company.",
    "options": [
      "treat",
      "raise",
      "link",
      "break",
      "reduce"
    ],
    "answer": "raise"
  },
  {
    "question": "Complete the sentence: Some people buy luxury products because such products … their status and give them a new, more upmarket",
    "options": [
      "target",
      "raise",
      "turn",
      "lease",
      "reduce"
    ],
    "answer": "raise"
  },
  {
    "question": "Match the sentence to a suitable ending. As they had an exciting idea to promote,…..",
    "options": [
      "and asked them to talk about innovation and change.",
      "they decided to exhibit at the Inventors` Fair.",
      "when they saw an opening in the market.",
      "when suddenly Jackson announced that he was stepping down as General Manager.",
      "and sold 3 million of the devices in 80 days."
    ],
    "answer": "they decided to exhibit at the Inventors` Fair."
  },
  {
    "question": "Complete the sentence: Agencies compete to win new contracts or take clients away from their…......",
    "options": [
      "breakthrough",
      "rivals",
      "competition",
      "accounts",
      "working conditions"
    ],
    "answer": "rivals"
  },
  {
    "question": "Choose the synonym for the word: respond",
    "options": [
      "carry out",
      "answer",
      "invest",
      "delegate",
      "believe"
    ],
    "answer": "answer"
  },
  {
    "question": "Complete the sentence: They only …. properties which are worth more than $1 million.",
    "options": [
      "liked",
      "search for",
      "fixed",
      "ask",
      "trades"
    ],
    "answer": "search for"
  },
  {
    "question": "Match the word to its definition. Someone whose job is to help two groups who disagree with each other to reach an agreement.",
    "options": [
      "client",
      "negotiator",
      "employee",
      "traders",
      "candidate"
    ],
    "answer": "negotiator"
  },
  {
    "question": "Complete the sentence: …..within the team are damaging operations at a property company.",
    "options": [
      "purchase",
      "tensions",
      "listening to others",
      "power",
      "flexibility"
    ],
    "answer": "tensions"
  },
  {
    "question": "Choose the right prepositions: That brings me …the end …my presentation.",
    "options": [
      "in, for",
      "on, to",
      "with, by",
      "to, of",
      "at, on"
    ],
    "answer": "to, of"
  },
  {
    "question": "Match the word to its definition. A lot of ideas and enthusiasm.",
    "options": [
      "ambition",
      "dynamism",
      "to brainstorm",
      "responsible",
      "intelligence"
    ],
    "answer": "dynamism"
  },
  {
    "question": "Match the word to its definition. The power to be physically and mentally active.",
    "options": [
      "ambitious",
      "energy",
      "stable",
      "honesty",
      "skilled"
    ],
    "answer": "energy"
  },
  {
    "question": "Complete the sentence. Now managers want to involve employees in a process of …..- getting everyone to participate in making",
    "options": [
      "workload",
      "consultation",
      "visionary",
      "bargain",
      "dynamism"
    ],
    "answer": "consultation"
  },
  {
    "question": "Match the word combination to its definition. A situation where most people agree with the decisions taken.",
    "options": [
      "controversial",
      "management by consensus",
      "tax incentives",
      "disagreement",
      "further discounts"
    ],
    "answer": "management by consensus"
  },
  {
    "question": "Match the word to its definition. Encouraging employees to use their own initiative to take decisions on their own without asking",
    "options": [
      "bargain",
      "empowerment",
      "negotiating",
      "after -sales-service",
      "cool off"
    ],
    "answer": "empowerment"
  },
  {
    "question": "Complete the sentence: The economy is stable…..the problems of the past two years.",
    "options": [
      "contacting",
      "following",
      "research",
      "discovering",
      "receiving"
    ],
    "answer": "following"
  },
  {
    "question": "Match the phrase to its definition. The way that negotiations develop.",
    "options": [
      "controversial",
      "bargaining process",
      "trade deficit",
      "warranty",
      "negative"
    ],
    "answer": "bargaining process"
  },
  {
    "question": "Match the word to its definition. Someone who is good at getting what they want, but could be difficult to deal with.",
    "options": [
      "free negotiator",
      "tough negotiator",
      "special negotiator",
      "better negotiator",
      "friendly negotiator"
    ],
    "answer": "tough negotiator"
  },
  {
    "question": "Match the verbs to the phrases: respond",
    "options": [
      "in regular training courses for employees",
      "to employees' concerns promptly.",
      "with colleagues clearly",
      "with problems quickly.",
      "in their employees' abilities."
    ],
    "answer": "to employees' concerns promptly."
  },
  {
    "question": "Match the verbs to the phrases: listen",
    "options": [
      "with problems quickly.",
      "to all suggestions from staff.",
      "with colleagues clearly",
      "in their employees' abilities.",
      "in regular training courses for employees"
    ],
    "answer": "to all suggestions from staff."
  },
  {
    "question": "Match the verbs to the phrases: deal",
    "options": [
      "to all suggestions from staff.",
      "with problems quickly.",
      "to a deputy as often as possible",
      "in their employees' abilities.",
      "to employees' concerns promptly."
    ],
    "answer": "with problems quickly."
  },
  {
    "question": "Match the word to its definition. To give other people responsibility for work rather than doing it all themselves.",
    "options": [
      "to issue",
      "to delegate",
      "to increase",
      "to deal",
      "to accept"
    ],
    "answer": "to delegate"
  },
  {
    "question": "Match the verbs to the phrases: believe",
    "options": [
      "to all suggestions from staff.",
      "with colleagues clearly",
      "in their employees' abilities.",
      "with problems quickly.",
      "to a deputy as often as possible"
    ],
    "answer": "in their employees' abilities."
  },
  {
    "question": "Match the verbs to the phrases: delegate",
    "options": [
      "in regular training courses for employees",
      "to a deputy as often as possible",
      "with colleagues clearly",
      "with problems quickly.",
      "in their employees' abilities."
    ],
    "answer": "to a deputy as often as possible"
  },
  {
    "question": "Match the sentence to a suitable ending. Apple released the first iPad in April 2010…..",
    "options": [
      "when suddenly Jackson announced that he was stepping down as General Manager.",
      "and sold 3 million of the devices in 80 days.",
      "that they were exhibiting at the Inventors` Fair.",
      "when they saw an opening in the market.",
      "they decided to exhibit at the Inventors` Fair."
    ],
    "answer": "and sold 3 million of the devices in 80 days."
  },
  {
    "question": "Complete the sentence: I’ll talk to the manager during the break if I … the chance.",
    "options": [
      "reduce",
      "get",
      "rise",
      "treat",
      "do"
    ],
    "answer": "get"
  },
  {
    "question": "159. Choose the right form of the verb-noun combination. To develop …..",
    "options": [
      "a need",
      "a business idea",
      "a breakthrough",
      "a range",
      "the environment"
    ],
    "answer": "a business idea"
  },
  {
    "question": "Choose the right form of the verb-noun combination. To extend …..",
    "options": [
      "advantage",
      "a range",
      "an award",
      "the environment",
      "a need"
    ],
    "answer": "a range"
  },
  {
    "question": "Choose the right form of the verb-noun combination. To win …",
    "options": [
      "a need",
      "an award",
      "a range",
      "a business idea",
      "the environment"
    ],
    "answer": "an award"
  },
  {
    "question": "Choose the right form of the verb-noun combination. To meet ….",
    "options": [
      "a breakthrough",
      "a need",
      "a range",
      "an award",
      "a business idea"
    ],
    "answer": "a need"
  },
  {
    "question": "Choose the right form of the verb-noun combination. To protect ….",
    "options": [
      "advantage",
      "the environment",
      "a range",
      "a breakthrough",
      "a business idea"
    ],
    "answer": "the environment"
  },
  {
    "question": "Choose the right form of the verb-noun combination. To take ….",
    "options": [
      "the environment",
      "advantage",
      "a breakthrough",
      "a range",
      "an award"
    ],
    "answer": "advantage"
  },
  {
    "question": "Choose the right form of the verb-noun combination. To make …..",
    "options": [
      "the environment",
      "a breakthrough",
      "an award",
      "a need",
      "advantage"
    ],
    "answer": "a breakthrough"
  },
  {
    "question": "Choose the right prepositions. Most ... the best ideas are discovered ... accident.",
    "options": [
      "on, to",
      "of, by",
      "with, on",
      "of, with",
      "in, by"
    ],
    "answer": "of, by"
  },
  {
    "question": "Make up the sentence: development/ is/ business/ the/ Research/ great/ key/ ideas/ and/ to",
    "options": [
      "Research and is great the development to ideas business key.",
      "Research and development is the key to great business ideas.",
      "Research is great to development ideas business and the key.",
      "Research and great the business to development is key ideas.",
      "Research great and the business is development to ideas key."
    ],
    "answer": "Research and development is the key to great business ideas."
  },
  {
    "question": "Match the word combination to its definition. To be in charge of a meeting.",
    "options": [
      "to bring forward a meeting",
      "to run a meeting",
      "to miss a meeting",
      "to set up a meeting",
      "to put back a meeting"
    ],
    "answer": "to run a meeting"
  },
  {
    "question": "Match the word combination to its definition. To go to a meeting.",
    "options": [
      "to set up a meeting",
      "to attend a meeting",
      "to put back a meeting",
      "to miss a meeting",
      "to run a meeting"
    ],
    "answer": "to attend a meeting"
  },
  {
    "question": "Make up the sentence: we/ useful/ felt/ had/ I/ very/ discussions/ some",
    "options": [
      "I had some discussions we felt useful very.",
      "I felt we had some very useful discussions.",
      "Some very useful discussions felt we had I.",
      "We very felt useful some I discussions had.",
      "Useful I very had discussions we some felt."
    ],
    "answer": "I felt we had some very useful discussions."
  },
  {
    "question": "Complete the sentence. Linda works in Research and Development. Her job..... developing new products and new ideas.",
    "options": [
      "deals",
      "involves",
      "looks",
      "makes sure",
      "is in charge"
    ],
    "answer": "involves"
  },
  {
    "question": "Complete the sentence: If an idea is really good and the product .... in the market, it may even win an award for innovation.",
    "options": [
      "spend a lot",
      "fills a gap",
      "goes green",
      "tests",
      "increase"
    ],
    "answer": "fills a gap"
  },
  {
    "question": "Choose the right prepositions: We collected information …..possible locations ….the new office.",
    "options": [
      "at, in",
      "about, for",
      "with, on",
      "to,at",
      "in, to"
    ],
    "answer": "about, for"
  },
  {
    "question": "Match the verbs to the phrases: communicate",
    "options": [
      "to employees' concerns promptly.",
      "with colleagues clearly",
      "to a deputy as often as possible",
      "in their employees' abilities.",
      "to all suggestions from staff."
    ],
    "answer": "with colleagues clearly"
  },
  {
    "question": "Match the verbs to the phrases: invest",
    "options": [
      "to employees' concerns promptly.",
      "in regular training courses for employees",
      "to all suggestions from staff.",
      "with problems quickly",
      "with colleagues clearly"
    ],
    "answer": "in regular training courses for employees"
  },
  {
    "question": "Complete these sentence with suitable preposition. I agreed ….her that we need to change our marketing strategy.",
    "options": [
      "in",
      "with",
      "at",
      "on",
      "about"
    ],
    "answer": "with"
  },
  {
    "question": "Complete these sentence with suitable preposition. I talk …. my boss every Monday at our regular meeting.",
    "options": [
      "at",
      "to",
      "with",
      "in",
      "of"
    ],
    "answer": "to"
  },
  {
    "question": "Complete these sentence with suitable preposition. We argued …..next year's budget for over an hour.",
    "options": [
      "of",
      "about",
      "in",
      "on",
      "at"
    ],
    "answer": "about"
  },
  {
    "question": "Complete these sentence with suitable preposition. He apologised ….losing his temper.",
    "options": [
      "of",
      "for",
      "on",
      "at",
      "in"
    ],
    "answer": "for"
  },
  {
    "question": "Complete these sentence with suitable preposition. We talked ….our financial problems for a long time.",
    "options": [
      "in",
      "with",
      "to",
      "on",
      "about"
    ],
    "answer": "about"
  },
  {
    "question": "Complete these sentence with suitable preposition. The Finance Director argued …. our Managing Director over profit sharing.",
    "options": [
      "on",
      "with",
      "in",
      "of",
      "at"
    ],
    "answer": "with"
  },
  {
    "question": "Complete these sentence with suitable preposition. I apologised …. Paula for giving her the wrong figures.",
    "options": [
      "in",
      "to",
      "at",
      "on",
      "with"
    ],
    "answer": "to"
  },
  {
    "question": "Complete these sentence with suitable preposition. Can we agree ……. the date of our next meeting?",
    "options": [
      "for",
      "on",
      "of",
      "in",
      "by"
    ],
    "answer": "on"
  },
  {
    "question": "Choose the right prepositions: Staff often complained ….the new manager, saying he didn`t believe …their abilities.",
    "options": [
      "to, for",
      "about, in",
      "at, by",
      "in, on",
      "with, to"
    ],
    "answer": "about, in"
  },
  {
    "question": "Choose the right prepositions: Robert was arguing ….his boss ….taxation.",
    "options": [
      "in, for",
      "with, about",
      "to, on",
      "by, at",
      "from, to"
    ],
    "answer": "with, about"
  },
  {
    "question": "Choose the right prepositions: Good. So you all seem to agree ….me ….the main points.",
    "options": [
      "for, at",
      "with, on",
      "from, to",
      "by, in",
      "in, from"
    ],
    "answer": "with, on"
  },
  {
    "question": "Choose the right prepositions: They apologised ….everyone ….their failure to deal ….the crisis.",
    "options": [
      "by, at, from",
      "to, for, with",
      "for, on, of",
      "by, in, on",
      "with, to, in"
    ],
    "answer": "to, for, with"
  },
  {
    "question": "Choose the right prepositions: The team had to report …..their progress ….the manager every month.",
    "options": [
      "in, from",
      "on, to",
      "for, at",
      "by, in",
      "for, on"
    ],
    "answer": "on, to"
  },
  {
    "question": "Choose the right preposition: Robert never listen …my suggestions.",
    "options": [
      "for",
      "to",
      "on",
      "in",
      "at"
    ],
    "answer": "to"
  },
  {
    "question": "Choose the right prepositions: My company spends a lot …money …training courses ….employees.",
    "options": [
      "from, to, in",
      "of, on, for",
      "by, at, in",
      "for, to, on",
      "for, at, by"
    ],
    "answer": "of, on, for"
  },
  {
    "question": "Choose the right preposition: He may become a good manager. It depends …his communication skills.",
    "options": [
      "in",
      "on",
      "of",
      "for",
      "by"
    ],
    "answer": "on"
  },
  {
    "question": "Make up the sentence: My/ ready/ wasn`t/ asked/ my/ why/ me/ boss/ report.",
    "options": [
      "My asked report me boss wasn`t my ready why.",
      "My boss report my wasn`t ready asked me my.",
      "My report wasn`t why asked me ready boss my.",
      "My boss asked me why my report wasn`t ready.",
      "My ready report my asked boss me wasn`t why."
    ],
    "answer": "My boss asked me why my report wasn`t ready."
  },
  {
    "question": "Match the verb to its meaning: to make a plan or drawing",
    "options": [
      "design",
      "discontinue",
      "distribute",
      "test",
      "launch"
    ],
    "answer": "design"
  },
  {
    "question": "Match the word or phrase to its definition: not spending more money than had been planned for",
    "options": [
      "spent",
      "keep within the budget",
      "break down",
      "contribution",
      "public spending"
    ],
    "answer": "keep within the budget"
  },
  {
    "question": "Match the word or phrase to its definition: bring something into existence",
    "options": [
      "remain",
      "found",
      "find",
      "grow",
      "live"
    ],
    "answer": "found"
  },
  {
    "question": "Complete the sentence. A small helium-gas cylinder… the airbag in 0.1seconds and is designed to let cyclists see at all times.",
    "options": [
      "runs",
      "inflates",
      "improves",
      "tests",
      "includes"
    ],
    "answer": "inflates"
  },
  {
    "question": "Complete the sentence: When the goods you require are not available they are …….",
    "options": [
      "confident",
      "out of stock",
      "dispatched",
      "rejected",
      "in stock"
    ],
    "answer": "out of stock"
  },
  {
    "question": "Complete the sentence: Goods are kept in our .... until ready for delivery.",
    "options": [
      "turnover",
      "warehouse",
      "bargain",
      "mail",
      "industry"
    ],
    "answer": "warehouse"
  },
  {
    "question": "Complete the sentence: Goods will be … within 24 hours of your order.",
    "options": [
      "purchased",
      "dispatched",
      "exchanged",
      "increased",
      "placed"
    ],
    "answer": "dispatched"
  },
  {
    "question": "Complete the sentence: A … is a company or a person that sells goods to members of the public.",
    "options": [
      "teacher",
      "retailer",
      "broker",
      "secretary",
      "purchaser"
    ],
    "answer": "retailer"
  },
  {
    "question": "Complete the sentence: If you buy goods in ….., you buy large amounts of them.",
    "options": [
      "service",
      "bulk",
      "minority",
      "credit",
      "refund"
    ],
    "answer": "bulk"
  },
  {
    "question": "Complete the sentence: In order to get a full … ,customers must send back goods in the original packaging.",
    "options": [
      "delivery",
      "refund",
      "storage",
      "discount",
      "bargain"
    ],
    "answer": "refund"
  },
  {
    "question": "Complete the sentence: A… is a large area where there are lot of shops, usually a covered area where cars cannot go.",
    "options": [
      "industry",
      "mall",
      "head office",
      "town",
      "restaurant"
    ],
    "answer": "mall"
  },
  {
    "question": "Complete the sentence: Products and services offered at a large discount are generally a (an) .… .",
    "options": [
      "sale",
      "bargain",
      "increase",
      "offer",
      "stock"
    ],
    "answer": "bargain"
  },
  {
    "question": "Complete the sentence: … means to send goods to a place .",
    "options": [
      "to walk",
      "to dispatch",
      "to improve",
      "to prepare",
      "to cover"
    ],
    "answer": "to dispatch"
  },
  {
    "question": "Complete the sentence: Do not … to contact us if you need further information.",
    "options": [
      "organize",
      "deliver",
      "offer",
      "hesitate",
      "open"
    ],
    "answer": "hesitate"
  },
  {
    "question": "Match the sentence to the right meaning expressed by the modal verb. We have to work very hard to reach our sales targets.",
    "options": [
      "It would be a good idea.",
      "It is necessary.",
      "It is against the law.",
      "It is not necessary.",
      "Don`t do that!"
    ],
    "answer": "It is necessary."
  },
  {
    "question": "Match the sentence to the right meaning expressed by the modal verb. You should order online, it`s more convenient.",
    "options": [
      "It is necessary.",
      "It would be a good idea.",
      "It is not necessary.",
      "Don`t do that!",
      "It is against the law."
    ],
    "answer": "It would be a good idea."
  },
  {
    "question": "Match the sentence to the right meaning expressed by the modal verb. You mustn`t show your PIN to anyone.",
    "options": [
      "It is necessary.",
      "Don`t do that!",
      "It is against the law.",
      "It would be a good idea.",
      "It is not necessary."
    ],
    "answer": "Don`t do that!"
  },
  {
    "question": "Match the sentence to the right meaning expressed by the modal verb. The supermarket is just down the road so we don`t have to take",
    "options": [
      "It is against the law.",
      "It is not necessary.",
      "It would be a good idea.",
      "It is necessary.",
      "Don`t do that!"
    ],
    "answer": "It is not necessary."
  },
  {
    "question": "Match the sentence to a suitable ending. My business is quite small,….",
    "options": [
      "so you must be confident.",
      "so I have to be very careful with cashflow.",
      "so you'll have to buy it on disk.",
      "so we don't need to work over the weekend.",
      "so I don't have to worry about a bank loan."
    ],
    "answer": "so I have to be very careful with cashflow."
  },
  {
    "question": "Match the sentence to a suitable ending. I can pay for the house now,…..",
    "options": [
      "so we must not offer any further discounts.",
      "so I don't have to worry about a bank loan.",
      "so you must be confident.",
      "so you'll have to buy it on disk.",
      "so I have to be very careful with cashflow."
    ],
    "answer": "so I don't have to worry about a bank loan."
  },
  {
    "question": "Match the sentence to a suitable ending. Our profit margin is low,….",
    "options": [
      "so I have to be very careful with cashflow.",
      "so we must not offer any further discounts.",
      "so you'll have to buy it on disk.",
      "so you must be confident.",
      "so we don't need to work over the weekend."
    ],
    "answer": "so we must not offer any further discounts."
  },
  {
    "question": "Match the sentence to a suitable ending. He`s arriving on Thursday 5th ….",
    "options": [
      "a non-smoking room.",
      "and leaving on the 7th in the morning.",
      "in the name of Robert Dorey.",
      "but not too expensive?",
      "it`s too far from the centre."
    ],
    "answer": "and leaving on the 7th in the morning."
  },
  {
    "question": "Choose the synonym of the word: arrange",
    "options": [
      "hesitate",
      "organize",
      "impose",
      "book",
      "impact"
    ],
    "answer": "organize"
  },
  {
    "question": "Complete the sentence: The chair really kept things moving - she encouraged people to ….to the point by keeping things brief.",
    "options": [
      "sale",
      "stick",
      "used",
      "around",
      "covered"
    ],
    "answer": "stick"
  },
  {
    "question": "Find the correct meaning of the word: to implement",
    "options": [
      "estimate costs",
      "to put a plan into action",
      "selling price minus direct production costs",
      "keep within",
      "the variable costs in marking particular goods"
    ],
    "answer": "to put a plan into action"
  },
  {
    "question": "Find the correct meaning of the word: to submit",
    "options": [
      "arrange a meeting",
      "to suggest or say something",
      "to leave a company",
      "buying and selling the money of particular countries",
      "to forecast profit"
    ],
    "answer": "to suggest or say something"
  },
  {
    "question": "Complete the sentence: Experts… the value of the deal at 20 million euros.",
    "options": [
      "arrange",
      "drawing up",
      "estimate",
      "mix",
      "stick to"
    ],
    "answer": "estimate"
  },
  {
    "question": "Choose the synonym of the word: an entrepreneur",
    "options": [
      "staff",
      "a businessman",
      "employer",
      "team",
      "a partner"
    ],
    "answer": "a businessman"
  },
  {
    "question": "Choose the synonym of the word: rescue",
    "options": [
      "launch",
      "save",
      "succeed",
      "plan",
      "admit"
    ],
    "answer": "save"
  },
  {
    "question": "Complete the sentence: Hieatt and his….....managed to rescue the situation bya catalogue to sell products.",
    "options": [
      "traders, turning",
      "colleagues, launching",
      "friends, plan",
      "rivals, sending",
      "consumers, fixed"
    ],
    "answer": "colleagues, launching"
  },
  {
    "question": "Complete the sentence: If something happens later than planned, it is …..",
    "options": [
      "referred",
      "delayed",
      "fixed",
      "forced",
      "demanded"
    ],
    "answer": "delayed"
  },
  {
    "question": "Match the word or word to its definition. A carefully planned piece of work to produce something new.",
    "options": [
      "mining",
      "a project",
      "workload",
      "a recession",
      "deadline"
    ],
    "answer": "a project"
  },
  {
    "question": "Choose the right prepositions. Lots …company employees go …time-management courses.",
    "options": [
      "in, to",
      "of, on",
      "on, in",
      "of, to",
      "of, in"
    ],
    "answer": "of, on"
  },
  {
    "question": "Choose the synonym of the word: calendar",
    "options": [
      "time",
      "diary",
      "stake",
      "organised",
      "share price"
    ],
    "answer": "diary"
  },
  {
    "question": "Match the word or word combination to its definition. Small pocket-size computers.",
    "options": [
      "time management",
      "personal organizers",
      "ethnic minorities",
      "remind",
      "upmarket"
    ],
    "answer": "personal organizers"
  },
  {
    "question": "Match the word or word combination to its definition. To put things in order of importance.",
    "options": [
      "decrease",
      "to prioritize",
      "to spend",
      "collect",
      "meet a need"
    ],
    "answer": "to prioritize"
  },
  {
    "question": "Choose the synonym of the word: interruption",
    "options": [
      "saturated",
      "distraction",
      "imports",
      "exports",
      "recession"
    ],
    "answer": "distraction"
  },
  {
    "question": "Match the word to its definition. Things which stop you doing what you had planned.",
    "options": [
      "promotions",
      "interruptions",
      "working for yourself",
      "exports",
      "bonuses"
    ],
    "answer": "interruptions"
  },
  {
    "question": "Match the verb to the noun: estimate",
    "options": [
      "to achieve",
      "costs",
      "research",
      "discover",
      "consider"
    ],
    "answer": "costs"
  },
  {
    "question": "Match the verb to the noun: forecast",
    "options": [
      "people",
      "sales",
      "receive",
      "discover",
      "informative"
    ],
    "answer": "sales"
  },
  {
    "question": "Match the verb to the noun: do",
    "options": [
      "research",
      "sales",
      "costs",
      "options",
      "information"
    ],
    "answer": "research"
  },
  {
    "question": "Match the verb to the noun: collect",
    "options": [
      "research",
      "information",
      "looks",
      "sales",
      "costs"
    ],
    "answer": "information"
  },
  {
    "question": "Match the verb to the noun: consider",
    "options": [
      "sales",
      "information",
      "research",
      "options",
      "costs"
    ],
    "answer": "options"
  },
  {
    "question": "Choose the right prepositions: I'm hoping to get a bonus…. the end …. the year.",
    "options": [
      "in, to",
      "to,at",
      "at, of",
      "on, in",
      "with, on"
    ],
    "answer": "at, of"
  },
  {
    "question": "Complete the sentence: The times or dates when things in a plan should happen are its ….",
    "options": [
      "quality",
      "turnover",
      "net profit",
      "upmarket",
      "schedule"
    ],
    "answer": "schedule"
  },
  {
    "question": "Match the verb to its meaning: to introduce to the market",
    "options": [
      "distribution",
      "discontinue",
      "test",
      "design",
      "launch"
    ],
    "answer": "launch"
  },
  {
    "question": "Match the verb to its meaning: to increase sales by advertising, etc.",
    "options": [
      "distribute",
      "launched",
      "manufacturing",
      "designer",
      "promote"
    ],
    "answer": "promote"
  },
  {
    "question": "Match the sentence to a suitable ending. It isn't available as a download,….",
    "options": [
      "so we must not offer any further discounts.",
      "so I have to be very careful with cashflow.",
      "so we don't need to work over the weekend.",
      "so you'll have to buy it on disk.",
      "so you must be confident."
    ],
    "answer": "so you'll have to buy it on disk."
  },
  {
    "question": "Match the verb to its meaning: to stop making",
    "options": [
      "manufacture",
      "discontinue",
      "continued",
      "design",
      "test"
    ],
    "answer": "discontinue"
  },
  {
    "question": "Match the verb to its meaning: to build or make",
    "options": [
      "discontinue",
      "manufacture",
      "launch",
      "start",
      "promoted"
    ],
    "answer": "manufacture"
  },
  {
    "question": "Match the sentence to a suitable ending. We've reached our sales targets,….",
    "options": [
      "so I don't have to worry about a bank loan.",
      "so we don't need to work over the weekend.",
      "so you must be confident.",
      "so we must not offer any further discounts.",
      "so you'll have to buy it on disk."
    ],
    "answer": "so we don't need to work over the weekend."
  },
  {
    "question": "Match the sentence to a suitable ending. The job involves sales presentations,….",
    "options": [
      "so I have to be very careful with cashflow.",
      "so you must be confident.",
      "so I don't have to worry about a bank loan.",
      "so we must not offer any further discounts.",
      "so you'll have to buy it on disk."
    ],
    "answer": "so you must be confident."
  },
  {
    "question": "Complete the sentence: We offer a … to customers who buy in bulk.",
    "options": [
      "delivery",
      "discount",
      "bargain",
      "refund",
      "storage"
    ],
    "answer": "discount"
  },
  {
    "question": "Complete the sentence: … means to give someone their money back, because they are not satisfied with what they have bought.",
    "options": [
      "to order",
      "to carry",
      "to refund",
      "to cover",
      "to damage"
    ],
    "answer": "to refund"
  },
  {
    "question": "Complete the sentence. The students .... work hard to pass the exam.",
    "options": [
      "will able to",
      "must",
      "are able",
      "haven't to",
      "had"
    ],
    "answer": "must"
  },
  {
    "question": "Match the verb to its meaning: to supply to shops, companies, customers",
    "options": [
      "test",
      "distribute",
      "design",
      "launch",
      "discontinue"
    ],
    "answer": "distribute"
  },
  {
    "question": "Complete the sentence. It comes with a full five-year .... on parts and labour.",
    "options": [
      "staff",
      "guarantee",
      "colleague",
      "expert",
      "place"
    ],
    "answer": "guarantee"
  },
  {
    "question": "Make up the sentence: should/ new/ immediately/ we/ test/ this/ product.",
    "options": [
      "This immediately new product should we test .",
      "We should test this new product immediately.",
      "Immediately we test should this new product.",
      "New this should we immediately test product.",
      "Should this we product test immediately new."
    ],
    "answer": "We should test this new product immediately."
  },
  {
    "question": "Make up the sentence: we/ have/ the/ improve/ definitely/ to/ packaging.",
    "options": [
      "To have packaging we improve the definitely.",
      "We definitely have to improve the packaging.",
      "Definitely to have the improve we packaging.",
      "To improve definitely the packaging have we.",
      "The have to packaging definitely improve we."
    ],
    "answer": "We definitely have to improve the packaging."
  },
  {
    "question": "Complete the sentence. Samsinite sells practical and well … bags and suitcases.",
    "options": [
      "card",
      "made",
      "safe",
      "find",
      "mode"
    ],
    "answer": "made"
  },
  {
    "question": "Choose the right prepositions. It's fairly expensive compared ….other models.",
    "options": [
      "on",
      "with",
      "by",
      "at",
      "in"
    ],
    "answer": "with"
  },
  {
    "question": "Complete the sentence: We ask consumers who are not fully satisfied to … goods within seven days.",
    "options": [
      "sale",
      "return",
      "discount",
      "delivery",
      "bargain"
    ],
    "answer": "return"
  },
  {
    "question": "Choose the right preposition. I hope this is suitable.....you.",
    "options": [
      "of",
      "for",
      "in",
      "at",
      "from"
    ],
    "answer": "for"
  },
  {
    "question": "Match the word or phrase to its definition: to say what you expect to happen in the future.",
    "options": [
      "decide",
      "forecast",
      "warned",
      "pretend",
      "say"
    ],
    "answer": "forecast"
  },
  {
    "question": "Choose the right prepositions. We are hoping to be the supermarket …...choice our country's football fans.",
    "options": [
      "to, at",
      "of, for",
      "to, for",
      "on, in",
      "of, in"
    ],
    "answer": "of, for"
  },
  {
    "question": "Match the sentence to a suitable ending. Make sure you know your product,",
    "options": [
      "you have less than 30 seconds",
      "it`s too far from the centre.",
      "before they form an opinion of you",
      "but not too expensive",
      "business and industry inside out."
    ],
    "answer": "business and industry inside out."
  }
]